<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<results>
    <cottages>
        <cottage position="1" type="C" code="2593" year="2025" name="Prospect Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.13052872" lon="-5.62063304" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/2593/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £328" changeover="Friday" town="Penzance" towndis="3.6 miles W of Penzance" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="327.6" maxRent="327.6" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="Two doggies are welcome to join you when you stay at cute as a button Prospect Cottage. This traditionally presented darling little terraced cottage, situated in far west Cornwall is ideally located for nature lovers, dog walkers and those escaping the humdrum. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Once you have driven up the little unmade lane parked up and unloaded the car, two granite steps lead into the open plan living-room with a wonderful warming French stove, perfect for lighting on cooler days making this a year-round destination. The charming, bijou kitchen area with delightful hand-made, hand-coloured tiles and artworks showcase the owners artistic flair and will surely inspire the designated chef to prepare a delightful dish for a memorable meal.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Upstairs is the double bedroom, decorated in relaxing, soft blue and cream hues to encourage a restful night of slumber, and a bathroom with fresh white suite for ablutions at the start and end of a busy day. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Really pretty courtyards to both the front and to the rear of the property are filled with potted plants brimming with ferns, flowers and foliage and provide a relaxing, peaceful spot for a morning coffee, an evening night cap or maybe somewhere to just sit and be. "/>
        <cottage position="2" type="C" code="4099" year="2025" name="Buzzard's Rise" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.19765909" lon="-5.19128635" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4099/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £345" changeover="Saturday" town="Falmouth" towndis="6.3 miles NW of Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="344.52" maxRent="344.52" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="A cosy hideaway for you and your dog; perfect for those wanting to get away and enjoy the peace and quiet of rural Cornwall with the stunning coastline less than half an hour away.  As the name suggests you can enjoy watching majestic buzzards rise over the hills beyond which is really quite magical.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Making your way to Buzzard's Rise through pretty lanes following a babbling stream, you feel the stress of life drifting away. Parking up in the large car parking area you are greeted by a lovely view and of course your cosy abode. Step into the property through the double doors into the light and airy reception room, you will instantly relax. Enjoy snuggling up on the sofa in front of your favourite film or read in comfortable silence from one of the books the owner has left for you to enjoy. Two steps lead up to the chic kitchen/diner, it is well-stocked for all your culinary needs and with calming views over the fields, it is a great place to eat your breakfast.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The double bedroom is at the far end of the barn with a modern flair and the only sounds are the hooting owls and perhaps a rustle of a badger outside, just bliss. The bedroom also has a bright, modern en suite shower-room which is very handy. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside, the barn has a private sitting-area with a table and chairs where you will be surrounded by wildlife and can watch the buzzards rise over the fields. There is also a lovely open lawned area where you can enjoy a chilled glass of wine in the evening light and perhaps enjoy a bit of bird watching and the dog can stretch their legs. The owner is on site but the property maintains its privacy, if you have any questions they are of course happy to help. "/>
        <cottage position="3" type="C" code="3859" year="2025" name="Little Tregerry" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.680035" lon="-4.526716" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3859/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £345" changeover="Friday" town="Crackington Haven" towndis="6 miles SE of Crackington Haven" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="345" maxRent="345" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="If you're looking for a peaceful break for two, you need look no further than Little Tregerry. Located down a country lane, in the heart of the Cornish countryside, with meadows, streams and wildlife all around, this is the perfect place to escape the hustle and bustle of everyday life yet be walking on the beach at Crackington Haven after a short drive to the coast, however should you wish to relax into your holiday abode and walk from the front door, you will not be disappointed!&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This charming little semi-detached bolthole has been sympathetically styled to compliment its surroundings whilst offering a comfortable open plan living-room on the ground floor, the perfect spot to indulge into a holiday read or cook up the perfect brunch on your first morning thanks to a fully equipped shaker kitchen. As night falls and the stars come out climb the stairs where you will discover a cottage-style bedroom and bathroom on the first floor. Outside, the small patio-area is an ideal spot to enjoy your morning coffee, afternoon tea or that all important sundowner. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Set in over 23 acres, the owners have been rewilding some of the land and there is a lovely newly planted arboretum for you to explore. Little Tregerry shares this perfect rural setting with neighbouring [Coombe Cottage (3858)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-3858.html &quot;Coombe Cottage&quot;), and the very helpful but discreet owners, along with their chickens, geese, Margigold and Millie the donkeys and of course, Boris, the Kunekune pig! "/>
        <cottage position="4" type="C" code="4976" year="2025" name="Poldhu" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.106742" lon="-5.572354" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4976/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per night £51 - £85" changeover="Friday" town="Mousehole" towndis="2.2 miles NW of Mousehole" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="50.72188" maxRent="85.382" rentPeriod="Daily" maxPets="1" introText="Enclosed by lush greenery and tropical foliage, you will discover Poldhu; a charming shepherd's hut perfect for those looking to escape the city and immerse themselves in nature. The surrounding garden features a huge variety of exotic plants and delicate flowers ensuring a unique retreat for anyone who visits. The hut's gorgeous, sun-soaked exterior is also complemented by a cosy, rustic interior meaning that rain or shine, there will always be somewhere to relax in this excellent one bed property.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Upon entering the hut, you will be greeted by an intimate interior full of character and charm. Freshly cut flowers and vibrant yellow curtains give the space a homely feel while the arched ceiling and superbly finished wooden walls cover the hut with extraordinary texture. A hugely inviting double bed sits snugly in the corner, topped with plenty of plush cushions to snuggle up with in the evening.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Wake up to the morning sun flooding through the double Dutch doors which open the space up to the freshness of its natural surroundings. Further down the hut you will find a compact kitchen with everything you will need for your cosy break. The beautiful wooden cabinets are accompanied by modern accessories such as a fridge/freezer, microwave and plug in hob, while the sturdy wooden work surface is the perfect place to prepare delicious meals. Alongside the kitchen is a charming dining-area. Enjoy relaxing breakfasts and cosy suppers on the rich wooden table and accompanying chairs while gazing out the window towards the idyllic garden.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Once with sun dips below the horizon, custom overhead lamps drench the space with their warm, restful glow, encouraging you to wind down after a busy day exploring the Cornish coastline. Select one of the complimentary books from the hand-crafted shelves or settle down on the luxurious bed and enjoy the flatscreen TV, perched above the dining-table at the end of the hut. Venture through the door located by the kitchen and you will find a delightful wood-clad bathroom with all the utilities you will need. Refresh yourself in the fabulous modern shower which accompanies a beautifully crafted toilet and sink. Outside, soak up the evening sun with the splendid garden right at your fingertips on Poldhu's raised deck.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Enjoy al fresco dining from the barbecue on the outdoor table and chairs, complete with a parasol, or take a moment on the rounded bench and listen out for the gentle trickling of the garden pond.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;There is another hideaway on site [Porth Chapel Cabin (4973)]( https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-4973.html &quot;Porth Chapel Cabin&quot;) and [Beryas Cottage (4970)]( https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-4970.html &quot;Beryas Cottage&quot;), but please note the properties are positioned in a way so you have plenty of privacy."/>
        <cottage position="5" type="C" code="4203" year="2025" name="Pinnock" xcode="206" brandCode="" lat="50.433216" lon="-4.519587" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4203/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £363" changeover="Friday" town="Looe" towndis="6.2 miles NW of Looe" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="362.5" maxRent="362.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Wind your way along country lanes to this truly delightful retreat that is just the tonic for those looking to enjoy precious time together and escape the humdrum of everyday life. Carefully designed for two, this super little cottage named after the parish in which it is located, is beautifully decorated and furnished throughout, ensuring that you completely relax in no time at all.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;From holiday breakfasts on the terrace to an evening stroll along the owners' woodland walk, you are sure to make the most of this tranquil setting and the great outdoors. Set between the owners' home and [Winwalloe Cottage (3774)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-3774.html &quot;Winwalloe Cottage&quot;) this is a great base for exploring the surrounding countryside and beautiful coastline of this relatively unknown part of Cornwall. With miles of coastal footpaths and an abundance of fishing villages and towns, great beaches, open moorland and so much more all within easy access, why would you choose to stay anywhere else?&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Step inside and you will be delighted – there's an open plan living-room with exposed beams, a comfy sofa to snuggle up on, contemporary very well-equipped kitchen and lovely artwork on the walls. Upstairs the romantic bedroom has a gorgeous king-size bed adorned with beautiful bed linen and of course piles of soft cushions and a stylish en suite shower-room ready to freshen you up for the day ahead. And just what will that day bring…"/>
        <cottage position="6" type="C" code="5238" year="2025" name="The Dairy" xcode="206" brandCode="" lat="50.43304445" lon="-4.51928616" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5238/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £368" changeover="Saturday" town="Looe" towndis="6.2 miles NW of Looe" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="368" maxRent="368" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="Nestled down a peaceful, leafy country lane, The Dairy is a charming country cottage, stylishly renovated to offer a romantic getaway or solo retreat, with easy access to the delights of the beautiful beaches and fishing villages of the south coast.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The Dairy is a delightful bijou abode, perfect for a well-deserved break at any time of year, and even your four-legged friend is welcome. Part of the small and secluded Lee Barton Cottages collection, you have the freedom to explore the delightful grounds and woodlands with just the sounds of the countryside to accompany you. The owners live on site and are available should you have any questions, and their two very friendly dogs are always happy to say hello!&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Step inside and the sitting/dining-room will instantly have you feeling at home, with the warm glow from the electric fire keeping you cosy when you snuggle up on the sofa. Down four steps the pretty kitchen awaits with all the equipment you will need to cook a holiday meal and those countryside views to admire through the window. The pretty bedroom on this floor has a comfy king-size bed for a restful night and the en suite has a shower cubicle, ideal after a busy day of exploring the delights of south Cornwall. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;From the sunny patio the sights and sounds of the countryside will keep you entertained from dawn until dusk, listen as you unwind in your tranquil surroundings. The large lawned area is shared with [The Stables (5239)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-5239.html &quot;The Stables&quot;) next door, each property has its own patio and these are out of sight of each other. You are welcome to explore the owners' grounds and surrounding woodland, and with a fabulous choice of walks from the cottage, your dog will be very pleased with your holiday choice!"/>
        <cottage position="7" type="C" code="5239" year="2025" name="The Stables" xcode="206" brandCode="" lat="50.43312646" lon="-4.51924324" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5239/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £368" changeover="Saturday" town="Looe" towndis="6.2 miles NW of Looe" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="368" maxRent="368" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="For a tranquil escape in a rather special setting, The Stables is just the place. Sleeping two, dog-friendly and tucked away in the glorious south Cornwall countryside, this cosy semi-detached cottage is sure to offer a peaceful holiday any time of the year.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;All on one level, the lovely and light open plan living space has a Shaker-style kitchen, perfect for preparing delicious breakfasts and suppers with fresh produce from the local farm shop, a sweet dining-table and chairs, and a comfortable sofa with a wood-burner effect electric stove - quite a treat on those chilly evenings! Next door, you'll find the beautifully dressed double bed with a stylish en suite shower-room. And with peaceful surroundings like these, long leisurely lie ins await…&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;From the living space, the patio doors open out to the sunny terrace along with the large lawned area, shared with the guests of [The Dairy (5238)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-5238.html &quot;The Dairy&quot;) next door. The countryside views here are rather special, just inviting you to sit back in the sunshine and soak them up. You're welcome to explore the beautiful woodland walks within the grounds, too. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The friendly owners live nearby, should you have any questions during your stay, and their two friendly dogs are likely to come and say hello when you arrive - the sweetest of welcomes, we think!"/>
        <cottage position="8" type="C" code="5959" year="2025" name="Hobbit Corner" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.444169398" lon="-4.53155350689" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5959/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £380" changeover="Friday" town="Looe" towndis="7.3 miles NW of Looe" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="379.5" maxRent="379.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Wind your way along the leafy lanes to the peaceful hamlet of Trevelmond, in the heart of southeast Cornwall, where this little beauty is waiting to welcome you with open arms and a warm Cornish embrace. Whether you are escaping for a few days or a longer stay, Hobbit Corner is a great base to discover all the delights this part of Cornwall has to offer. From the sun-kissed beaches, clifftop walks and charming waterside towns and villages of the south coast to the wild beauty of Bodmin Moor, it's all within easy access.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Behind the unassuming façade of this charming single-storey cottage, prepared to be wowed by the most gorgeous interiors where every detail has been thoughtfully curated in a countryside inspired palette with luxury at the very heart.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Enjoy a cosy evening in, curled up on the sofa with a good book with the dancing flames of the wood-burning stove creating a warm and inviting glow and share a glass of wine over a delicious supper at the sweetest of dining-tables. The kitchen is a true delight- beautifully designed and fully equipped with everything you need to whip up your holiday feasts and the little breakfast-bar is perfect for casual bites and morning chats.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The super-comfy king-size bed is dressed to impress, layered with luscious linens plump cushions and throws, it's the perfect excuse for a lie-in and when you are finally ready to rise and shine, the shower-room offers Villeroy and Boch fittings and a large shower to set you up for the day ahead.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Perfect for both couples, solo adventurers and your four-legged friend, check yourself in to Hobbit Corner and treat yourself to a well-deserved escape."/>
        <cottage position="9" type="C" code="5600" year="2025" name="Blue Mill Retreat" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.3395823" lon="-4.6344599" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5600/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £393" changeover="Friday" town="Fowey" towndis="Fowey" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="392.5" maxRent="392.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="For out-of-season breaks or lazy summer stays, come and immerse yourself in the Fowey way of life at the stylish Blue Mill Retreat. Fowey is a magical place, surrounded by beautiful countryside and scenery. It's the place to rewind and re-energise, so spend your days enjoying stunning coastal walks, lazy lunches in waterside eateries and having some fun on the water.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Tucked away at one end of the town, at the back of the Blue Mill Building, Blue Mill Retreat is really tranquil, yet only a short and easy walk to everything this trendy sailing town has to offer, and a mere hop and skip to the Bodinnick Ferry for when you want to venture further afield. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The epitome of a treasured bolthole, this ground floor apartment is perfect for solo travellers and couples alike. Step inside where warm and welcoming interiors await, beautifully presented with great attention to detail. With a large hallway, cosy, open plan living area, a tranquil bedroom with a separate dressing-room, and a sleek, no expense spared bathroom, Blue Mill Retreat really packs a punch. From the living-room you can access the sheltered terraced area. Shared with two other apartments, there are different levels and areas so you can all enjoy some space of your own. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Fowey is a vibrant coastal town with higgledy-piggledy terraced cottages perched on the hilly, narrow streets leading down to the water. There are many activities throughout the year, with Regatta Weeks, the Fowey Festival of Words and Music, the Fowey River Big Gig and BBQ Weekend, and Christmas Markets. Mosey around the boutiques, art galleries, and independent shops, stopping at one of the many places to eat and drink for some refreshments along the way. Fowey is a popular destination with sailors, with hundreds of yachts and boats bobbing on their moorings. The water is the playground here and if you fancy joining in, book yourself a sailing lesson or hire some kayaks and paddleboards and go off exploring the waterways under your own steam. Ferries cross to Polruan, Bodinnick and Mevagissey so why not hop aboard and see where they take you? &#xD;&#xA;"/>
        <cottage position="10" type="C" code="5585" year="2025" name="Honeysuckle Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.54987156" lon="-4.75905418" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5585/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £395" changeover="Saturday" town="Port Isaac" towndis="4.4 miles SE of Port Isaac" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="395.0001" maxRent="395.0001" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="This endearing cottage is ideal for a truly wonderful holiday in north Cornwall. So whether you're a walker, a beach lover, a fan of coastal villages and harbours, a foodie, a couple or a solo adventurer, come and escape to Honeysuckle Cottage. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Utterly charming and super cosy, this semi-detached cottage retains many of its traditional features with exposed beams, a huge inglenook fireplace, sloping ceilings (please mind your head) and very thick walls, that create wonderful window seats. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Behind the whitewashed exterior is a surprisingly spacious cottage with a toasty wood-burner taking centre stage in the sitting/dining room, a charming bedroom with a super-king size bed, a useful utility-room and a country-style kitchen. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside, relish the chance to relax, soaking up the sunshine on the terrace from your first cuppa of the morning, until sundowners; and don't forget your four-legged friend because they are going to simply love the enclosed garden. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Set along a country road, near the village of St Tudy, you can pop up to the popular community farm shop and cafe to collect your morning pastries, and when you want someone else to cook up your dinner delights, the gastro pub will not disappoint. "/>
        <cottage position="11" type="C" code="5707" year="2025" name="Rose's Loft" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.05146" lon="-5.09733" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5707/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £395 - £400" changeover="Friday" town="Porthallow" towndis="Porthallow" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="395.097" maxRent="400.099" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="With pastoral views of the surrounding woodland and within serpentine splendour, the conversion of this milking barn took place in 2021 to create a stunning bijou abode. Located a two-minute drive or a ten-minute walk to the pretty fishing village of Porthallow, which is the mid-way point on the South West Coast Path. Also, within the iconic Fat Apples site which has a beautiful community energy yet boasts an exclusively private feel with its own entrance, Rose's Loft is a truly unique hideaway for two lucky guests and is named after the owner's mother, Rose Jourdan (nee Paynter). Rose was related to Colonel Paynter, a characterful landowner that resided at Boskenna House near St Buryan. Although Rose spent her life living in Devon, she truly loved Cornwall and followed the Newlyn School of Painters, a group of artists based near Newlyn from the late 1800's till the early 20th Century. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Ascend the ten steps to your external canopied entrance vestibule, kick off your walking boots or beach shoes and be welcomed by the serene and neutral palette of your humble living space. The petite space is open plan and includes a mini kitchen for whipping up a light breakfast, brunch or supper, a comfortable lounge area and private dining space should you wish to use it, complete with divine glass door perfect for letting both the light and the fresh country air flood in.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The bedroom is spacious and has a comfortable double bed, plenty of hanging space and a brand new shower-room with glow mirror. There is an interconnecting door to the neighbouring property, but rest assured this is completely soundproof and private.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;There is an abundance of surrounding land to enjoy at Rose's Loft. This is communal with the very small and friendly campsite that is also on site. There's a wealth of places to settle down with a good novel on a sun lounger or with a picnic under the towering canopies, or by the natural pond where geese, ducks, ducklings and goslings reside. This land is eco conscious and the habitat for the wildlife is encouraged with wildflower meadows and a safer space for the flora and fauna to thrive, yet you still have plenty of space to park your vehicle ahead of your Cornish adventures. The best of both worlds!  The Fat Apples site is home to one of the most iconic eateries on The Lizard peninsula, so most guests tend to indulge in the beautiful food that is offered here."/>
        <cottage position="12" type="C" code="2523" year="2025" name="Beacon Top Bottom" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.30640403" lon="-5.2143922" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/2523/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £400" changeover="Friday" town="St Agnes" towndis="St Agnes" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="400" maxRent="400" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="A cosy little bolthole nestled in the rugged countryside of the north coast. Ideally located to explore this stunning area of Cornwall, only a five-minute drive to the beautiful beaches of Chapel Porth and Trevaunance Cove and half a mile from the pretty village of St Agnes with a plethora of pubs, cafes, takeaways and shops. What more could you need for your break?&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Follow the path from the car parking space (about 50 meters away) and up the beautiful granite steps which lead up to the entrance. Receive a whole-hearted welcome when you open the door into the cosy open plan living-room, which is warmed by a wood-burner and styled with vintage, eclectic fabrics and furnishings. There is a simple kitchen-area with a hob and combination microwave which is sufficient but also a good reason to make the most of the local eateries. From the first floor you have far-reaching views across fields and countryside, you might also spy a chough or two in the fields which are part of the owners' organic smallholding where they produce their own vegetables, fruit and organic goats' milk (you may see the owners at work while you enjoy your morning coffee).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Following the stairs down, you will find the cosy bedroom and shower-room. The bedroom has such a snug feel with a charming vintage bedframe but of course top quality mattress, heavy quilts and warming hues for a peaceful night's slumber. The shower-room has a large walk-in shower which is perfect for a refreshing yourself after a day exploring the coast path. Open the stable door out to a sheltered patio (which is fully enclosed and dog escape proof) with a sitting-area covered with a glass roof. The perfect spot to put your feet up with a refreshing beer on the deck chair at the end of the day. "/>
        <cottage position="13" type="C" code="3774" year="2025" name="Winwalloe Cottage" xcode="206" brandCode="" lat="50.43308479" lon="-4.51918409" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3774/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4 + cot" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £401 - £472" changeover="Friday" town="Looe" towndis="6.2 miles NW of Looe" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="400.775" maxRent="471.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Tucked down a leafy lane with birdsong in the air, the rural tranquility of this pretty semi-detached cottage will delight those looking for a break from busy daily lives. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Just inland from the coast and set next to Pinnock (4203) and along from the friendly owners' home, Winwalloe Cottage is an ideal retreat from which to explore the lovely countryside and coastal areas of this relatively undiscovered part of Cornwall. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The cottage dates back to the 18th Century and has been updated in the most sympathetic way to provide lovely, comfortable holiday accommodation, decorated throughout in soft relaxing colours. The boot-room, perfect for drying off dogs or damp children after a day on the beach, leads into the well-equipped kitchen/diner where a rustic pine kitchen table provides the ideal space for leisurely meals. An open archway goes through to the cosy sitting-room where you can toast your toes in front of the open fire. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Stairs lead up from the kitchen/diner to the two good-sized bedrooms – one with a king-size bed and the other with twins – and family bathroom. Outside, the sheltered patio is a great spot for evening drinks and star-gazing on clear, balmy nights. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;One medium or two small, well-behaved dogs are most welcome, so your canine family members can also enjoy a wonderful Cornish holiday."/>
        <cottage position="14" type="C" code="4191" year="2025" name="The Old Dairy" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.24043736" lon="-4.79477978" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4191/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £403" changeover="Friday" town="St Austell" towndis="6.9 miles S of St Austell" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="403" maxRent="403" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="This former Cornish creamery has been converted into a delightful coastal retreat for two. Situated on the edge of the picturesque fishing village of Gorran Haven, The Old Dairy is a ten minute walk from the sheltered harbour and beach where kayaks and paddleboards can be hired. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The semi-detached cottage welcomes a dog and keen walkers will enjoy the scenic coastal walk to Mevagissey, or why not pack up a picnic and walk to the beautiful Vault Beach and Dodman Point for the day. The Barley Sheaf in Gorran is a short 5-minute drive or 15-minute walk away, a lovely spot for lunch or to enjoy an early evening drink. Cakebreads has a great bakery selection and bites to eat, the shop is open year-round so worth a visit in any season. "/>
        <cottage position="15" type="C" code="5121" year="2025" name="Pheasant Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.189842" lon="-5.1984289" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5121/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £410" changeover="Friday" town="Falmouth" towndis="6.4 miles NW of Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="410.28" maxRent="410.28" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Welcome to Pheasant Cottage, a cute as a button Cornish cottage nestled in a rather lovely location close to the village of Stithians. Perfect for two, this dog-friendly retreat is a wonderful spot to whisk your favourite person away, at any time of the year.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Step inside to find your cosy and welcoming getaway. The beautiful kitchen is ideal for cooking up delicious holiday meals, with a lovely dining space to enjoy them. The bijou sitting-room is just gorgeous, with its beamed ceilings and cottage charm, and promises those well-deserved relaxing evenings after a day of exploring. Light the wood-burner, pour a glass of your favourite tipple and sink into the squishy sofa and listen to your favourite tunes on the mini Hi-fi with Bluetooth and USB connection thoughtfully provided for your enjoyment. You'll also find the shower-room on the ground floor, decorated in calming, coastal blue tones. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Head upstairs to discover the wonderfully restful double bedroom, styled in pretty pastel colours and sure to provide a restorative night's sleep - ready for tomorrow's adventures. Outside there is a lovely sunny patio; a lovely space to soak up the Cornish sunshine and enjoy your morning coffee or supper, or simply spend an hour or two relaxing with your chosen holiday read.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;And as for the location, it's just perfect for explorers. Located on a side road leading into Stithians, the area's stunning landmarks are within easy reach either by car or by foot. Stithians Lake is right on your doorstep, inviting unforgettable outdoor adventures. There are plenty of water sports to choose from, including kayaking, paddleboarding and windsurfing, and you can also enjoy a leisurely walk around the lake and sunny picnics on the grass. You'll also find the wonderful Wild Vibes Cafe here, ideal for a delicious breakfast or tasty lunch, and coffee and cake too."/>
        <cottage position="16" type="C" code="5316" year="2025" name="The Nest" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.01717079" lon="-5.09654045" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5316/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £413" changeover="Friday" town="Coverack" towndis="Coverack" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="413.4" maxRent="413.4" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="One of a collection of fabulous apartments located in The Headland in the traditional Cornish fishing village of Coverack, The Nest is a beautifully furnished bijou abode, perfect for either a couple's getaway or a solo retreat and ideally placed to explore the best of The Lizard and west Cornwall.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The porch area at The Headland is communal with the additional benefit of a laundry-room, which is pay per use. The Nest is situated on the first floor of this grand residence and you will feel at home from the moment you step over the threshold. The sitting-room is stylishly furnished with cosy sofas around the log-effect electric fire, making this the ideal getaway throughout the year. For evenings in, the Smart TV and Sky Sports channel will keep you entertained and do take a look at the fabulous artwork on the walls, these gorgeous images were taken by the owners during their travels to the Galapagos Islands. A dining-table is tucked away in a corner, the perfect spot to chat over dinner or play a board game perhaps. The small kitchen is separate and has all you need to cook a holiday meal.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Through to the bedroom and what a delight it is! Decorated in cool white and complemented by beautiful painted oak furniture, you are assured of a restful night here. The shower-room is ideal for a refreshing shower after a busy day of exploring. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside, there are spacious communal gardens with stunning sea views to explore and a tennis court which you are welcome to use and rackets are available in the apartment. "/>
        <cottage position="17" type="C" code="5968" year="2025" name="The Barn at Little Windsor" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.41491045776" lon="-4.46719206406" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5968/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £415" changeover="Friday" town="Looe" towndis="4.3 miles N of Looe" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="414.7025" maxRent="414.7025" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Nestled in the exceptionally pretty Looe valley, with wonderful views across the rolling countryside, come and immerse yourself in Cornish charm, rural bliss and a wonderful wildlife haven at this delightful barn conversion for two and your tail wagging friend.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Set on the outskirts of the little village of St Keyne and only four miles from the coastal footpaths and the seaside town of Looe, The Barn at Litle Windsor serves up the perfect blend of coast and countryside. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This lovingly restored retreat offers a warm welcome from the friendly owner who lives on site - ready to assist if needed, but always respectful of your privacy. From the moment you arrive, you're invited to relax and unwind in their little slice of heaven and take life at a gentler pace. Start the day with a morning cuppa in the garden, enjoy a lazy lunch in the sunken terrace or stargaze with your favourite tipple in hand, with the songs of the birds serenading you throughout your day. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Inside reverse level accommodation is the order of the day, to make the most of the views. On the ground floor, the bedroom is adorned with lovely linens that perfectly complement the setting and here you will also find the shower-room, convenient not just for your morning shower but should you want to come in and rinse off straight away after a day on the beach or a countryside ramble.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Upstairs you'll find the open plan living-room, the place to settle down for cosy moments on the sofas and when it's time to dine, you are promised a table with a view at every meal. The sweet kitchen comes equipped with all you need to prepare that nourishing 'Full English', holiday picnics and savoury suppers with some fresh produce picked up from a local farm shop."/>
        <cottage position="18" type="C" code="3842" year="2025" name="Lee Cottage" xcode="206" brandCode="" lat="50.43307454" lon="-4.51926455" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3842/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4 + cot" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £415 - £488" changeover="Friday" town="Looe" towndis="6.2 miles NW of Looe" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="414.851" maxRent="488.06" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="What a delightful getaway this is, set down a tree-lined lane amid the tranquility of beautiful countryside. With rustling leaves and birdsong as a background lullaby, you will relax and unwind in no time at all. Lee Cottage is a single-storey barn conversion, light-filled and facing out over its own secluded garden.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;There is a big open plan living-room with archways leading through to the garden room, running the length of the cottage, so plenty of space to spread out.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This tucked-away corner of Cornwall is less well-known, but with countryside all around and the beautiful south coast close by, this is a lovely location. Lee Cottage is perfect for families, couples and dog walkers, with woodland and coastal footpaths, superb beaches and easy access to good roads for exploring further afield.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;After days out and about, you'll love returning home and relaxing in the garden to the sound of birdsong or in front of the warming wood-burner in cooler months.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The friendly owners live across the courtyard and are happy to welcome you and offer advice if requested but equally happy to leave you to yourselves so you can relax in peace and quiet. The owners' two friendly dogs will come to say hello when you arrive, offering a warm welcome of their own!"/>
        <cottage position="19" type="C" code="4093" year="2025" name="West Barn" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.16396935" lon="-5.29722977" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4093/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £417" changeover="Friday" town="Porthleven" towndis="5.5 miles N of Porthleven" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="416.9632" maxRent="416.9632" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="One of a pair of detached barn conversions tucked away in the tranquil hamlet of Crowan, as soon as you pull into the drive, you feel as though you have stepped in to a story book. The craftsmanship here is very special and the thatched roofs set the scene for a beautiful rural escape from the hubbub of everyday life.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The exposed beams, high ceilings and wooden floors give the barn a calm environment for your holiday. The charming open plan living-room has a modern kitchen, light living space with comfy sofa (which converts into a sofa bed) and we feel this is the perfect spot for relaxing on holiday and enjoying the peace and quiet of the cottage. The bedroom with en suite shower-room is on the left as you enter the property, the high ceilings give the bedroom a lovely airy feel. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside the front door is a pretty private sitting-area with a table and chairs, you can sit and unwind while you listen to the bird song with a cup of tea or a glass of wine, whichever takes your fancy. The property sits in 10 acres of grounds which the owners invite you and your neighbours at East Barn to explore and use at your leisure. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;From the grounds you can access footpaths to discover the local area with no need to get into the car. The owners are very friendly and helpful, and should you have any questions or if you would like any recommendations they would be happy to help."/>
        <cottage position="20" type="C" code="3207" year="2025" name="Cowries" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.1786258" lon="-4.97309025" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3207/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £427" changeover="Sunday" town="Portscatho" towndis="Portscatho" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="426.715" maxRent="426.715" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Cowries is a cosy ground floor apartment sleeping two with fabulous uninterrupted views of Gerrans Bay and the pretty seaside village of Portscatho. Situated directly above the harbour and virtually at the end of the Lugger – a row of predominantly traditional stone-built fishermen’s cottages – the apartment is one of a small number set back from a no-through road, which has very little passing traffic. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The village centre with a general store, pub, cafe and galleries is a short level stroll away, and the harbour and beach are likewise immediately to hand. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The apartment (with its own designated parking space) is approached by a short flight of steps from the private parking-area to the front of the property. There is access at the rear to a small secluded gravelled-area; this is a useful space to store kayaks, bikes, etc."/>
        <cottage position="21" type="C" code="4649" year="2025" name="Celtic Reach" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.6243766" lon="-4.679987" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4649/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £427 - £474" changeover="Saturday" town="Camelford" towndis="Camelford" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="426.87" maxRent="474.3" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Perched above the market town of Camelford with commanding views that stretch out to the rugged landscape of Bodmin Moor, this charming pad is only the shortest of drives to the stunning north Cornish coast. Bring the whole family along to be part of this holiday adventure, whether you plan fun-filled days on the beach, a brisk stomp across majestic moorland and coastal footpaths, leisurely lunches at harbourside pubs and cafes or exploring historic houses and gardens, there really is something for everyone.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Decorated throughout in relaxing shades of grey, punctuated with flashes of colour, open plan living is the order of the day to maximise your time together and make the most of the view. Patio doors draw you to that view and lead out to the fab decking-area where meals can be savoured in the fresh air or a lazy afternoon spent chilling in the hammock.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;When it's time for bed, the three bedrooms promise a good night's sleep, setting you up ready for the next day's adventure."/>
        <cottage position="22" type="C" code="5998" year="2025" name="Copper Bal Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.1255612" lon="-5.43332593" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5998/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 3 + cot" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £427 - £474" changeover="Saturday" town="Marazion" towndis="1.9 miles E of Marazion" location="" maxAdults="3" minRent="426.915" maxRent="474.35" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Nestled in the picturesque Cornish village of Goldsithney, just moments from the coast and the hidden gem of Prussia Cove, Copper Bal Cottage is a delightful dog-friendly, two bedroomed terraced cottage which is the perfect escape for couples or a small family seeking comfort, charm and a real taste of Cornish life. Thoughtfully furnished and full of character, the cottage blends modern comfort with a warm welcoming feel, sleeping three guests wishing to explore this stunning part of the county.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Inside this sweet home, the snug sitting-room's central focus is the cosy wood-burner, perfect for curling up by after a day exploring the coast or countryside. Comfy sofas and a huge armchair invite you to settle in on a chilly evening and appreciate the homely feeling. The well-equipped modern kitchen caters for all your needs with stylish crockery and quality cookware. The bright and airy dining-area is a social space to gather sharing a relaxed breakfast, long lunches or intimate suppers. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Doors open directly onto a sweet two-tiered garden. A bistro table offers a tranquil spot for morning coffee whilst in the garden there is also relaxed seating thoughtfully placed for unwinding with a book or soaking up the Cornish sunshine. You can also fire up the barbecue and enjoy al fresco dining of a summer evening. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Up the traditionally steep cottage stairs there are two bedrooms, one with a luxurious king-size bed, full of natural light and one is a small double, both beautifully appointed for a restful night's sleep. A small but stylish bathroom sits between the two, ideal to wash away your sandy day."/>
        <cottage position="23" type="C" code="5116" year="2025" name="Chybean" xcode="210" brandCode="" lat="50.187715" lon="-5.06352" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5116/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £432" changeover="Friday" town="Falmouth" towndis="2.4 miles N of Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="431.9" maxRent="431.9" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="A quaint and cosy Grade II Listed cottage, set in a tranquil beautiful location on a family-run farm.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This charming cottage has lots of little quirky features due to its age, from the sheltered courtyard where you park your car, to the stable-door into the small but perfect formed kitchen (please watch the step and mind your heads) which has everything you might need for a feast of local treats. The kitchen leads up to the cute sitting/dining-room that overlooks the sunny and sheltered front garden. In the winter, enjoy snuggling up together on the sofa watching a film using the Amazon Fire TV Stick, enjoying the warmth of the flickering flames of the wood-burner after a brisk countryside walk, or in the warmer months leave the front door open and enjoy the balmy breeze.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Upstairs you will find the lovely bedroom also looking over the front garden. Fall asleep with the windows open listening to the hooting owls and the dawn chorus, what could be more relaxing. There is also a handy sink in the bedroom and the shower-room is found downstairs, just off the kitchen, so perfect for washing those sandy toes at the end of the day.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;The enclosed garden at Chybean is a lovely spot to sit back and relax with your four-legged friend catching the sun most of the day. The footpaths are abundant and right from your front door; set in an Area of Outstanding Natural Beauty and surrounded by the waters of Carrick Roads there is so much to explore. There is a pretty estuary shingle beach only 300 yards down the hill from the cottage, perfect for taking a paddleboard down and exploring these waters.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;This lovely location is shared by the adjoining cottage [Chyvounder (5117)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-5117.html &quot;Chyvounder&quot;), which is ideal should you want to holiday with your extended family or group of friends. If you love the water this is the perfect place for you, the owners are able to offer by separate arrangement (on availability) a mooring which is only 300 yards from the property and boat storage, there is also handy launching very nearby and at Mylor Harbour too."/>
        <cottage position="24" type="C" code="4242" year="2025" name="Little Woon" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.131445" lon="-5.202158" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4242/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £442 - £491" changeover="Thursday" town="Falmouth" towndis="6.2 miles W of Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="441.612" maxRent="490.68" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Welcome to the ultimate piece of paradise for couples looking to escape on a get-away-from-it-all break. Set in a secluded spot yet close to all that this gorgeous corner of Cornwall has to offer, this idyllic retreat was originally used for boat building and has been lovingly refurbished - with a great focus on upcycling and sustainable tourism - to create the cosy, tranquil and comfortable home-from-home that it is today.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This stunning retreat is a true hideaway, hidden behind the original barn doors - open them up to reveal the entrance, step in and your holiday begins. Enter straight into the sumptuous open plan living area, complete with snuggly sofa, TV and wood-burner - ideal for cosy evenings in, and a beautiful kitchen, equipped for all of your holiday needs, including an electric cooker, microwave, fridge (with ice-box) and kettle. There is also a dining-area, where many a scrumptious supper can be enjoyed, accompanied by a glass of wine or two. Your only neighbours are the lovely owners who live on site and very occasionally use the office space above the barn.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;A sliding door opens to reveal the delightful bedroom and its inviting super king-size bed (this can also be configured as twin beds), made up with a white feather down duvet and plumped up pillows - the perfect place to rest your head after a day out and about exploring. There is also a large wardrobe with plentiful hanging space and a chest of drawers, so you won't be short of storage. From the bedroom, another sliding door leads to the spacious shower-room with its heated towel rail and under-floor heating to keep your toes toasty in the cooler months.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;But that's not all - outside, reached via patio doors in the living area, is your very own pretty garden (it's enclosed, so great for your four-legged friend). Here you can snooze in the sun, dine al fresco on the decking or cook up a storm on the fire-pit barbecue until your heart's content, all whilst taking in some good ol' fresh air and savouring the great outdoors.">
            <specialOffers>
                <specialOffer title="Special Offer - 10% off" dates="30 Oct 2025 to 6 Nov 2025" priceFull="Full Rent £491.00" priceNow="Now £441.90"/>
            </specialOffers>
        </cottage>
        <cottage position="25" type="C" code="4176" year="2025" name="Meadow Barn" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.740999" lon="-4.549417" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4176/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £443" changeover="Friday" town="Bude" towndis="6.1 miles S of Bude" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="442.5" maxRent="442.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Whether you’re a walker, a lover of nature and the coast or you simply want to unwind and spend time together then look no further than Meadow Barn. Nestled in the heart of the countryside, this gorgeous single-storey barn conversion oozes comfort and tranquility and is perfect for couples seeking a restful haven. You can spend your days relaxing on the terrace, lazing in the wild flower meadow or wandering through the woodlands and getting at one with nature. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Reached along a private drive, this lovely location is only a few minutes from Cornwall’s north coast with coastal footpaths, superb beaches, pretty fishing villages and towns waiting to be discovered and with great access to good roads for exploring further, what more could you want.&#xD;&#xA;"/>
        <cottage position="26" type="C" code="5840" year="2025" name="The Dolls House" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.3365986999" lon="-4.6369067379" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5840/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £448" changeover="Friday" town="Fowey" towndis="Fowey" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="447.5" maxRent="447.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Retreat to our stylish little cottage for two, nestled in the popular sailing town of Fowey, set at the mouth of the magnificent Fowey Estuary. As perfect for relaxing breaks or romantic getaways, The Dolls House is an oasis of calm with exquisite interiors and a sunny courtyard, yet only the shortest of walks down the hill to the vibrant town centre.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Pull up to your private parking space directly outside, a real bonus for Fowey, and then step inside your holiday home where a warm Cornish welcome awaits. Reversed-level living is the order of the day, with the en suite bedroom on the ground floor, so much more convenient for unpacking suitcases and travel bags. The large open plan living-room spreads across the whole of the first floor. It's a wonderfully light and airy room with a vaulted ceiling, and whilst sat at the dining-table enjoy glimpses of the estuary and surrounding countryside, along with the 15th Century tower of Place House, from the window.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;If you want to soak up the sun, head outside to the little courtyard. It's the perfect spot to relax with your morning coffee or treat yourself to an afternoon tea - jam first of course."/>
        <cottage position="27" type="C" code="2557" year="2025" name="Wheel Barn" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.31996066" lon="-4.96860742" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/2557/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £450" changeover="Saturday" town="Truro" towndis="5.3 miles NE of Truro" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="449.5" maxRent="449.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="A wood-burner and under-floor heating ensure year-round snugness in this lovingly restored, single-storey converted barn, found near the hamlet of Ladock in an easily accessible rural setting. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Impeccably furnished and decorated, Wheel Barn provides an ideal base for exploring while offering comfort for those wishing to stay in and relax. The open plan living-room has chestnut leather sofas and French doors to an enclosed patio and garden with far reaching views over the Ladock valley. Two steps lead down from the dining-area to the fully-equipped kitchen. Beautifully styled, the bedroom also has doors opening out to the garden, and is adjacent to the spacious shower-room. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The hospitable owners live next door and are happy to welcome two well-behaved medium-sized dogs."/>
        <cottage position="28" type="C" code="5484" year="2025" name="Stable Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.33290878" lon="-4.81454372" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5484/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £450" changeover="Friday" town="St Austell" towndis="1.1 miles SW of St Austell" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="450" maxRent="450" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Nestled in the tranquil hamlet of St Mewan with views of the pretty church, this is a rather special holiday hideaway. Perfect for a solo holiday adventure or that romantic stay with a loved one, Stable Cottage offers stylishly comfortable luxury living over two floors.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Head up a short flight of steps and you enter through a wooden porchway into the first floor open plan living space, which is thoughtfully styled in relaxing hues of creams and greys to complement the beautiful herringbone wooden floor and quality furnishings throughout. Relax on the fabulous sofa after a day out exploring, snuggle up in front of the Smart TV to watch your favourite movie or listen to music, create a culinary masterpiece or a tasty snack or head out to one of the local pubs, the Polgooth Inn is only a short drive away as is the Cornwall Spa if you fancy booking yourself a pamper. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;When the clock strikes bedtime, head down the stairs to your stunning bedroom where you will find a super-king size bed and an en suite bathroom with walk-in shower and free-standing double ended bath, ideal for a soak at the end of the day - whether you've had an active day walking the coast path or spent a more relaxing day closer to home. Open the French doors and take your bedtime nightcap or morning cuppa out onto your little private courtyard. There's a further private outdoor sitting-area opposite the cottage, a more sheltered space which is perfect to retreat to on a hot sunny day with a cold drink.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Whether a short break visit or a longer stay, this little gem of a holiday cottage may just leave you coming back for more."/>
        <cottage position="29" type="C" code="4910" year="2025" name="2 Belgravia" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.11949" lon="-5.5369" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4910/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 3 + cot" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £451 - £474" changeover="Friday" town="Penzance" towndis="Penzance" location="" maxAdults="3" minRent="450.6325" maxRent="474.35" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="Perfectly located just a short walk from the delights of central Penzance and with the stunning coast of far west Cornwall a stroll away, 2 Belgravia is a beautifully renovated mid-terraced cottage, ideal for a small family (babes in arms up to six months old are welcome), or a couple looking for a romantic getaway. With miles of gorgeous coastline, hidden coves and sandy beaches waiting to be discovered, along with pretty fishing villages and a wonderful choice of fabulous eateries, let your holiday dreams come alive in this gorgeous bolthole.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Located up four granite steps, 2 Belgravia is simply gorgeous. The moment you step over the threshold you will instantly feel at home. From the beautiful oak flooring to the fabulous contemporary wood-burner, everything has been thought of to make your stay comfortable. Super comfy sofas invite you to relax with gorgeous artwork and well-placed lamps completing the stylish look. The farmhouse kitchen table sits at the far end of the living area where you can sit and make plans for the day ahead. The kitchen sits at the back of the cottage, small but perfectly formed, you will find everything you need here to create a holiday feast. The staircase is a work of art! With a well-positioned porthole giving a nod to this seafaring land, each steep step has been painted in gorgeous turquoise blue hues of the ocean. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;On the first floor you will find two beautifully styled bedrooms and the family bathroom. Just off the landing, one small step takes you into the double bedroom which is oh so pretty. With double sash windows, painted floorboards and a beautiful brass bedstead this really is a bedroom of sweet dreams. The pretty single bedroom is perfect for either an adult or child. The family bathroom has a gorgeous claw-foot free-standing bath with rainfall shower over, perfect for either a long soak or a refreshing shower after a busy beach day. Outside you have a bijou courtyard with bistro table and chairs, the perfect spot for al fresco dining from dawn until dusk. 2 Belgravia has everything you need and more for a perfect Cornish getaway."/>
        <cottage position="30" type="C" code="5745" year="2025" name="Pink Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.12672" lon="-5.43598" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5745/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £452 - £502" changeover="Friday" town="Marazion" towndis="1.8 miles E of Marazion" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="451.71" maxRent="501.9" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="Tucked away in the heart of the bustling village of Goldsithney is this cute retreat, a lovingly restored cottage perfect for small families or couples. Arty and characterful, Pink Cottage welcomes you in a traditional Cornish setting.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Step inside to find numerous original features and lots of charm. The sitting-room is a joy and has plenty of comfy seating and a toasty wood-burner, perfect for cosy evenings in catching up on the day's adventures. The owners' interior design shines through in every detail. Through the doorway is the well-equipped kitchen and dining area for four, beautiful local crockery sits on the shelves, sit back and relax with your morning coffee enjoying the simple joy of the local surroundings.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Upstairs you will find two beautiful bedrooms, to the right step up into a king-size bedroom with views of the quintessential English garden and to the left, step up into a sweet room with bunk-beds. A stylish family bathroom separates the two.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside the garden does not disappoint, a gravel courtyard leads to an enclosed area of lawn with plenty of outdoor furniture, benches, ornate tables and chairs and a charming summer-house so sit back and catch the sun. Light the barbecue and eat al fresco as this garden is a perfect place to relax.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;If you decide to eat out, the village has two excellent pubs both with tempting menus. A handy local shop is also just around the corner with a traditional tea-room. A bus service runs through this delightful village if you feel like leaving the car."/>
        <cottage position="31" type="C" code="4511" year="2025" name="Little Bambaroo" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.13195613" lon="-5.52172408" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4511/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £452 - £460" changeover="Friday" town="Marazion" towndis="Marazion" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="452.0975" maxRent="459.517" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="What a little cutie! Picture-perfect and utterly charming, this delightful bolthole for two is set deep in the heart of the quaint Cornish village of Churchtown Gulval. Spot the 12th Century Church and you have arrived!&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;A very pretty little path (with ten little steps) leads through the enchanting garden filled with succulents and other subtropical plants, which thrive in this part of Cornwall. Take a moment to enjoy this beautiful garden, before stepping through the front door into Little Bambaroo. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Brimming with character and style this gorgeous open plan retreat has everything you need for a relaxing stay, with a roaring wood-burning stove to make things super-cosy on those chillier evenings, and a comfy double bed at the far end of the room. You will also find a delightful little dining-area and kitchenette for those who want to cook up a breakfast or a light supper. In the daytime you can sit and dream at the table gazing out the window as you linger over your morning cuppa. A single step takes you into the deceptively spacious shower-room, complete with a large shower cubicle, a must for washing sandy toes and salty hair. Outside the cottage has a glorious south-facing decked area with a table and two chairs perfect for a spot of al fresco dining.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Little Bambaroo is so welcoming you will feel lost in idyllic countryside bliss and may not wish to venture too far. Travelling around this gorgeous part of west Cornwall, the impossibly quaint village of Mousehole and working harbour of Newlyn are most definitely worth a visit. Spend a carefree day mooching around the enchanting little side streets and galleries, before stopping to pick up some local fish from one of the many fish stalls in Newlyn on your way home."/>
        <cottage position="32" type="C" code="5601" year="2025" name="Trebah" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.103489" lon="-5.38338" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5601/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £453" changeover="Saturday" town="Praa Sands" towndis="Praa Sands" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="453.15" maxRent="453.15" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="With a beautiful sandy beach only two minutes' walk away and spectacular sea views from the large picture window in the sitting area, Trebah is a surprisingly spacious studio apartment, perfect for a summer stay or a cosy winter break storm watching. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Open plan living and high ceilings bring light into this welcoming ground floor apartment and with a separate kitchen and dining-room, king-size bed, and spacious bathroom, this is a very comfortable property for two. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The building itself was an hotel once upon a time but is now home to the owner and guests at Trebah. The entrance to Trebah is accessed through a secluded courtyard with a bistro table and chair set. Enjoy a perfectly lazy start here with a morning coffee or traditional cup of builders whilst you plan your activity for the day. The terrace and swimming pool below belong to the owner who is handily nearby and happy to answer any questions or advise on the best places to visit. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Stroll down the hill to the beach or further on to the delightful beach bars and cafes which wrap around Praa Sands beach. It would be hard to beat the location of this little treasure sitting just above the beach in an elevated position."/>
        <cottage position="33" type="C" code="4751" year="2025" name="Little Jenny Wren" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.06700324" lon="-5.15100667" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4751/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per night £65 - £101" changeover="Friday" town="Helford" towndis="1.8 miles S of Helford" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="64.74236" maxRent="101.0795" rentPeriod="Daily" maxPets="1" introText="A cosy retreat for a romantic getaway close to the River Helford, this cute cabin has far reaching views across the Cornish countryside and is tucked away from the hustle and bustle of everyday life. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The open plan layout allows the day to effortlessly flow; enjoy a long breakfast in bed perhaps with the fire crackling on a winter's eve or a luxurious brunch at the dining-table looking over the valley with the doors open and the spring birdsong delighting your ears. The bed is tucked around the corner for a tranquil night's sleep with just the owls and lowing cows to keep you company. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The owners have lovingly created this lovely space with no details amiss; hand-crafted ceramics, a custom headboard created from locally-sourced trees and little touches throughout. There is plenty of outside space to relax at Little Jenny Wren, the private patio is the perfect spot for a barbecue, perhaps with freshly caught mackerel for supper. There is also a large lawned area which is all yours, perfect for a little picnic or just relaxing on a blanket with a good book. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Little Jenny Wren is found at the end of a farm lane, the cows and working farm dog are likely to greet you on your drive down through this working Cornish dairy farm. The friendly owners live on site and will give you a warm welcome but of course ensure your privacy during your stay."/>
        <cottage position="34" type="C" code="4314" year="2025" name="Orangery Lodge" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.359325" lon="-4.174247" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4314/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £455" changeover="Friday" town="Torpoint" towndis="1.5 miles SE of Torpoint" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="455.0002" maxRent="455.0002" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Orangery Lodge is a romantic retreat made for two!&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Located on the edge of Mount Edgcumbe, there are over 865 glorious acres of parkland, woods, coastline and Listed gardens for you to explore right on your doorstep, along with the historic house, cafes and artisan shops. It really is a very special place.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Dating back to the 16th Century, once the celebratory archway to the formal gardens of the Earl, this Grade II Listed gateway has been brought bang into the 21st Century with charming interiors,  befitting of any Earl, embracing the botanical theme that accentuates the overall character of the building.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;From leisurely holiday breakfasts in the stylish four-poster bed, to morning coffee on the elevated garden platform looking out across the waters of Plymouth Sound, or cosy evenings snuggled up on the sofa, Orangery Lodge promises a truly relaxing escape for wonderful times together.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Located at the bottom entrance of the Park where visitors access the gardens and Orangery Garden Cafe, with views from the sitting-room and garden across the waters of Plymouth Sound, shut the world behind you as you step into this stunning little oasis."/>
        <cottage position="35" type="C" code="3214" year="2025" name="Cremyll Lodge" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.36011392" lon="-4.17528816" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3214/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £455" changeover="Friday" town="Torpoint" towndis="1.7 miles SE of Torpoint" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="455.0004" maxRent="455.0004" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Nestled in its own garden within the Mount Edgcumbe Country Park, this is a charming retreat. The park has 865 acres of woods, fields and coastline – your dog will be in heaven! &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Originally part of staff accommodation provided by the Earl of Mount Edgcumbe, Cremyll Lodge is a comfortable and attractive cottage. There are views across Plymouth Sound from the sitting/dining-room, a kitchen, shower-room and an exceptionally pretty bedroom found up the steep stairs. A private entrance leads to the enclosed patio ensuring privacy from the little shop and cafe next door and the children’s play-area. The Rame Peninsula, known to locals as ‘the forgotten corner of Cornwall’, is a truly glorious part of the world."/>
        <cottage position="36" type="C" code="5283" year="2025" name="Cobble Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.8757803039964" lon="-4.48475238519856" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5283/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 5 + 2 cots" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £455 - £506" changeover="Saturday" town="Bude" towndis="4.1 miles NE of Bude" location="" maxAdults="5" minRent="455.4" maxRent="506" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="Kilkhampton is a charming Cornish village, perfectly placed for exploring the delights of north Cornwall and Cobble Cottage is a lovely terraced abode, situated in a quiet courtyard opposite the village square with traditional inns and food shops all close at hand as well as a well networked bus route!&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Whether you are looking to explore the stunning beaches of Bude just a short drive away, travel further afield to the gorgeous villages of Clovelly and Tintagel or stay closer to home and explore the pretty countryside around Kilkhampton, Cobble Cottage has all you need for a fabulous holiday no matter the season.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Accessed via a passageway from the village square, from the moment you arrive you will be captivated by the charm of Cobble Cottage. The cosy sitting-room has a fabulous feature inglenook fireplace, complete with wood-burner to keep you warm throughout the seasons and a Smart TV for your evening's entertainment. The kitchen/diner is perfect for sociable dining and has all the equipment you will need to create a culinary delight. The ground floor has a reclaimed brick floor with the joy of under-floor heating perfect for keeping your toes warm, and characterful beams throughout.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Stairs with handrail lead to the first floor, please note these are typical of traditional Cornish cottages and are steep. On reaching the top there are additional steps into the bedroom as well as the landing leading to bedrooms two and three and the family bathroom. Bedroom one is a charming, spacious room with comfy king-size bed and iron bedstead that floods with light thanks to the double-aspect windows. Bedroom two is a pretty single room perfect for young or old and offers a peaceful spot to enjoy the holiday read. Bedroom three is the perfect twin ideal for either children or adults. Please note there is a small lip/step up into this room, this bedroom has views out to the front of the cottage. The family bathroom has a lovely hand-made suite with a bath and fitted shower over.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;To discover the hidden enclosed garden simply wander down a beautiful path/track where just 90 yards away you will discover the private tranquil garden, perfect for relaxing in your countryside surroundings. A patio area with garden furniture provides a spot for you to fire up the barbecue and enjoy al fresco dining, and the thoughtful owners have created a wildflower area too. There's oodles of space for the children and family dogs to let off steam however please note the summer-house is not for guests' use. On the way down to the garden you will also pass the utility-room for keeping your outdoor gear or beach equipment. It also houses all the barbecue equipment, picnic plates and dishes; the owners have thought of everything."/>
        <cottage position="37" type="C" code="5864" year="2025" name="Little Blue" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.16907834" lon="-5.10555804" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5864/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £458" changeover="Friday" town="Falmouth" towndis="2 miles NW of Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="458.079" maxRent="458.079" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="In the heart of the historic yet trendy town of Penryn and only a five minute drive to Falmouth is this perfect bolthole for two. Named one of the best towns to live in in the South West by the Sunday Times, we are sure you will enjoy discovering what this pretty location has to offer.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Tucked away down a charming little street in the historic centre of the town, Little Blue is such a peaceful terraced property. One granite step takes you over the threshold where you are met with a light and airy entrance with plenty of room for your holiday essentials. To your left is the sitting/dining-room which overlooks the pretty courtyard garden; enjoy long relaxing breakfasts basking in the morning sun and in the evening snuggle up on the sofa in front of the wood-burner after a day exploring. Please note the Smart TV offers streaming services only and does not have terrestrial channels (remember to bring your login details for the streaming apps).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The little kitchen has everything you might need to create a feast and has a fabulous ground coffee machine to make the perfect morning brew. The kitchen opens onto the sunny courtyard garden which catches the sun throughout the day in the summer months. Upstairs you will find the pretty bedroom and bathroom. The bedroom is at the rear of the house to ensure peace and quiet for your holiday slumber and again catches the morning sun, so enjoy a cup of Cornish tea in bed before you start the day. The bathroom is perfect for a relaxing soak in the tub after a day exploring but also has a handy overhead shower to refresh you after your night's sleep.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside you'll find the good sized courtyard garden, quite the sun-trap in the summer months, perhaps perch on the bench against the house for a coffee at the start of the day, or head up a couple of steps to the main patio where you can enjoy long lunches. The owner has provided a charcoal barbecue so you can cook up some local produce, such as fresh fish from Seabourne Fish in the town, or something yummy from Baileys Country Store farm shop. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;While there isn't any parking at Little Blue you can drive down the narrow street (only suitable for small and medium-sized cars) and stop outside to unload your luggage. There is on street parking in Penryn or a car park only 200 yards from the house."/>
        <cottage position="38" type="C" code="1384" year="2025" name="Chy Goff" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.62928132" lon="-4.67614203" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/1384/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4 + cot" bedrooms="0" rent="Price per week £459 - £541" changeover="Saturday" town="Camelford" towndis="Camelford" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="459.425" maxRent="540.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Set down a Cornish country lane, detached Chy Goff is a pretty stone cottage that sits perfectly in tune with its surroundings. Steps lead down to the garden and entrance; inside, it's full of simple charm and home-from-home informality. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Character exudes from the slate-flagged floors and beamed ceilings, a green Aga complementing the rustic feel. The kitchen leads to the sitting/dining-room, which has a multi-burner, satellite TV from which you can access your Netflix account and French doors opening out to the sheltered garden. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;From the sitting/dining-room, a step takes you to a small study and a shower-room. Traditional cottage stairs lead to the bedrooms and bathroom, which enjoy countryside views. Outside, the small garden has a little stream, and extends to a rear patio that catches the evening sun."/>
        <cottage position="39" type="C" code="4997" year="2025" name="Pippin" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.18978286" lon="-5.06053984" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4997/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per night £66 - £110" changeover="Friday" town="Falmouth" towndis="2.5 miles N of Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="65.69927" maxRent="110.006" rentPeriod="Daily" maxPets="2" introText="A truly romantic getaway tucked in the corner of a luscious meadow with exclusive sea views; this fabulous shepherd's hut really is the ultimate destination.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Nestled in the beautiful countryside in a dreamy location, with only the wildlife as your neighbours and a quiet tidal beach only moments away, you will not want to leave Pippin's warm and welcoming arms. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;As you approach your destination through verdant lanes in this Outstanding Area of Natural Beauty you will feel like a true traveller, which is the meaning of Pippin. As you leave your car in the charming old quarry and walk up through the wildflower meadow you will see Pippin awaiting your arrival and the view over the tranquil estuary open up in front of you.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This truly unique and private location really has all you need; bask in the morning sun with your morning coffee on the hand-carved love seat after your morning dip or take a perch on the steps perhaps. There is a fabulous fire-pit perfectly set up for two, where you can enjoy a true fire cooked meal or perhaps toast your marshmallows and gaze at the stars together. The meadow provides plenty of space and is a great spot to have a picnic in the gentle summer sunshine. This is the perfect place for your four-legged friends to run free too but please be aware at certain times of year there are cattle in the other half of the meadow - this will be fenced off but please take care. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Inside this charming hut there is ultimate comfort - sink into the cosy double bed with only the rustling trees to lull you to sleep, the bench seat provides the perfect spot to sit and look at the view on the cooler days but fear not as there is a little wood-burner to ensure you are kept toasty at any time of year. Luxury has not gone amiss with of course an en suite loo and shower at Pippin.">
            <specialOffers>
                <specialOffer title="Special Offer - 10% off" dates="7 Nov 2025 to 14 Nov 2025" priceFull="Full Rent from £65.70" priceNow="Now from £59.13"/>
                <specialOffer title="Special Offer - 10% off" dates="14 Nov 2025 to 21 Nov 2025" priceFull="Full Rent from £65.70" priceNow="Now from £59.13"/>
                <specialOffer title="Special Offer - 10% off" dates="21 Nov 2025 to 28 Nov 2025" priceFull="Full Rent from £65.70" priceNow="Now from £59.13"/>
            </specialOffers>
        </cottage>
        <cottage position="40" type="C" code="6025" year="2025" name="Tea By The Sea" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="49.98776966" lon="-5.18018782" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/6025/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 5 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £461 - £513" changeover="Friday" town="Cadgwith" towndis="Cadgwith" location="" maxAdults="5" minRent="461.25" maxRent="512.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Less than a minute's stroll from the sea, this characterful two-storey apartment offers a wonderfully laid-back base for exploring Cadgwith, the picturesque little fishing cove that it sits in the heart of.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Step inside and you'll find a practical ground floor with a twin bedroom, a cosy single and the family bathroom. Upstairs, you are welcomed in by a beautiful light and open plan living space which makes the most of its elevated position with a lovely large window and sights of the sea framed between the historic cottages of the courtyard. The sitting and dining area is ideal for relaxing in after a day by the coast. The cosy well-equipped kitchen is perfect for preparing simple evening meals, while a welcoming king-size bedroom completes the first floor accommodation.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;What truly sets this home apart is its location. Just outside the front door, you can hire a kayak and set off on an adventure across the bay or just relax by the water's edge where fishing boats bob on the water and the pub welcomes you with hearty food and local ale."/>
        <cottage position="41" type="C" code="4784" year="2025" name="The Pigsty" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.065782" lon="-5.66566" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4784/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 3 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £462 - £513" changeover="Friday" town="Porthcurno" towndis="1.6 miles N of Porthcurno" location="" maxAdults="3" minRent="461.7" maxRent="513" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Countryside charm and vintage elegance rolled into one, The Pigsty is a perfect romantic getaway or retreat for a little family holiday as it sleeps up to three lucky guests. The Pigsty is a spacious, luxury bolthole and oozes effortless style and comfort from the moment you walk inside; it's set in a cluster of similar barns and snuggled at the end of a sheltered lane just outside the sleepy hamlet of St Levan.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Arrive and walk down the charming little path, taking in the stunning countryside that surrounds you. Walk into the spacious kitchen with its Belfast sink and oak work surfaces, hang your coats on the coat pegs beside the door and instantly relax. The sitting-room is flooded with light and has a comfy sofa and pre-loved rocking chair basking in the toasty warmth of the wood-burner so you can stretch out after a day walking the coastal footpaths or exploring the many art galleries in west Cornwall.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;A charming antique dining-table and wooden chairs nestle between the sofas and kitchen, perfect for long lunches and laid back intimate suppers. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The Pigsty has just the one family bedroom with an elegant mix of old and new, this bright and light room houses a comfy double bed and day bed (perfect for a younger child). There's a delightful shower-room to wake you up in the morning or to cool down after a day out exploring. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Stable-doors lead out from the open plan living-room onto the gorgeous, enclosed patio, sheltered by an old Cornish hedge. Overlooking fields where you may spot the odd cow or sheep (as The Pigsty is located on a working farm) this is the perfect spot for a pre-dinner G&amp;T.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;"/>
        <cottage position="42" type="C" code="2870" year="2025" name="Littlecott" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.68623561" lon="-4.69479876" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/2870/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £464" changeover="Friday" town="Boscastle" towndis="Boscastle" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="464" maxRent="464" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Littlecott is an ideal bolthole for exploring all the delights in and around Boscastle. The accommodation is very comfortable (and includes a king-size bed), bright and light with a fresh contemporary feel, and has beautiful elevated views out across the village which are a treat for the eyes.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Snuggled next to the friendly yet discreet owners' home, it is only a short walk down the steep hill into the heart of the picturesque harbour and you will be able to spend hours just relaxing, eating and exploring this charming and historical village. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Littlecott is a walker's paradise; the walks direct from the doorway lead you straight out onto the coastal path where miles of coastline may be explored."/>
        <cottage position="43" type="C" code="2995" year="2025" name="1 North Parade" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.17952446" lon="-4.97508734" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/2995/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £465" changeover="Friday" town="Portscatho" towndis="Portscatho" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="465.4" maxRent="465.4" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="This is a gorgeous little bolthole, right in the middle of lovely Portscatho on the Roseland peninsula and just yards from Tatam's beach (and Tatam's boutique cafe selling delicious coffee, croissants and cakes). &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Beautifully decorated and wonderfully comfortable, 1 North Parade will delight all who stay. Local artwork, rugs, cushions and throws all add to the feel good factor and together with the warming wood-burner make the cottage as inviting in cooler months as it is in spring and summer. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;There are glorious coastal walks right from the doorstep, with Tatam's beach a few steps away and the renowned Hidden Hut cafe at Porthcurnick Beach just a seven minute walk along the coast. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The nearby Plume of Feathers serves great locally-sourced food and offers a blazing log fire in chilly months, the perfect way to end the day.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This terraced cottage has a ground floor bedroom with hints of quirky nautical style in the porthole windowed doors and canvas sail used as a room divider. The shower-room has a big walk-in shower, Moroccan tiles and a useful drying/dressing-area. Upstairs, the open plan living-room is light and airy with painted floorboards, a warming wood-burner and an antique pine dining-table and pew. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The galley kitchen has Shaker-style units, oak work surfaces and lots of little extras like cookery books for those who like a spot of holiday cooking, along with a Nespresso coffee machine (please bring your own pods). A bespoke hamper awaits your arrival with Cornish tea and coffee, Cornish biscuits, Rodda's milk and butter, St Mawes' hens eggs and a fresh loaf of bread."/>
        <cottage position="44" type="C" code="5362" year="2025" name="Ivor's Barn" xcode="236" brandCode="" lat="50.1494889" lon="-5.5265522" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5362/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4 + cot" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £466 - £518" changeover="Saturday" town="Marazion" towndis="2.4 miles N of Marazion" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="465.75" maxRent="517.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="Ivor's Barn is a gorgeous stone-built barn perched on a hillside above the small village of Gulval in the far west of Cornwall. Restful rural surroundings with an ancient village, castle and sea close by… that's the lovely little mix you'll find at this charming abode. Sleeping four, this rather lovely barn is a wonderful choice for a family getaway or a romantic holiday for two, and your favourite pooch is more than welcome to join you! &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This gorgeous barn offers reverse level accommodation to take full advantage of the countryside and distant sea views. Arrive and walk into the spacious hallway hang your coats on the coat pegs and relax. Take the stairs up to the open plan living area. The fabulous kitchen has everything you might need for cooking up a breakfast feast or preparing a picnic to take with you to the beach. Relax at the breakfast-bar with your morning coffee and enjoy long, lazy lunches and sociable suppers at the dining-table. The sitting-area is flooded with light and has two comfy sofas basking in the toasty warmth of the wood-burner so you can stretch out after a day walking the St Michaels Way or coastal footpaths or exploring the little shops in St Ives. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;On the ground floor you will find two bedrooms that wouldn't look out of place in a boutique hotel. No expense has been spared, and the lovely owner has made sure that you have the best night's sleep, with each bed adorned in luxury linens and locally sourced natural throws. The contemporary family shower-room has a wonderful shower which is perfect for washing away salty hair and sandy toes. You will also find the oh so handy washing machine on this floor too. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside, there's a private patio which is stepped in places and perfect for soaking up the sunshine during the day, al fresco dining and gathering around the fire-pit at night under the starlit sky.&#xD;&#xA;"/>
        <cottage position="45" type="C" code="2389" year="2025" name="Smugglers Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.0783824" lon="-5.27947371" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/2389/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £468" changeover="Saturday" town="Porthleven" towndis="1.8 miles SE of Porthleven" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="467.5" maxRent="467.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="A cosy rural retreat for two on the edge of the National Trust’s beautiful Penrose Estate, Smugglers Cottage nestles quietly beside a handful of similar stone dwellings in a truly peaceful setting at the end of a private unmade lane. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;After each day’s adventure, the living-room's big squashy sofa will invite you to lounge in front of the wood-burner. Stairs lead to the pretty bedroom and the bathroom, which has a step up to the bath.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside is a private enclosed terraced garden, and a few yards away there is a picnic table in the grassed parking enclosure – perfectly placed for sunset watching or dining al fresco alongside horses grazing quietly in the nearby fields. RNAS Culdrose provides some entertainment with helicopters occasionally flying nearby, and the historic town of Helston provides all essential amenities."/>
        <cottage position="46" type="C" code="3959" year="2025" name="Cuddle Cabin" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.13168929" lon="-5.16154452" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3959/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £475" changeover="Friday" town="Falmouth" towndis="4.6 miles W of Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="474.92" maxRent="474.92" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="**£100 off any week-long booking between 31st October 2025 - 5th December 2025. Please use code SALE100 when booking.**&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Just as the name suggests this cabin is a perfect spot for a romantic weekend for two. Hidden away in a secluded corner of the owners' smallholding with just the chickens for company and the nature of the Cornish countryside. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Cuddle Cabin is found down a tree-lined path where, when you spot your hideaway, you will see a large outdoor seating area which is a wonderful place to relax. Enjoy a refreshing glass of champagne in the early evening glow or perhaps watch for shooting stars on a winter's eve whilst toasting marshmallows on the fire-pit. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Inside this cosy cabin you will see that no detail has gone amiss; a squishy L-shaped sofa is perfect to snuggle up on in front of the fire or enjoy a good film. The kitchen has everything you might need for a tasty meal or perhaps enjoy exploring this rural part of Cornwall and see what hidden culinary treasures you might find. The calming bedroom has a luxurious dressing-room to keep the bedroom as tranquil as possible and of course an en suite shower-room. Both the living space and bedroom have double doors that open onto your decking, enjoy wandering out in your fluffy dressing gown with your morning coffee and listening to the birds. "/>
        <cottage position="47" type="C" code="4043" year="2025" name="The Sheep Shed" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.20324619" lon="-5.22096191" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4043/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £476" changeover="Saturday" town="Falmouth" towndis="7.7 miles NW of Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="475.6" maxRent="475.6" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="The Sheep Shed is a delightful bolthole for couples, ideal for those who want to get away from the stresses of everyday life. Lovingly converted by the owners, this former farm building provides a great base for exploring this beautiful area of Cornwall and gives easy access to the beaches and attractions on the north, south and west coasts.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Set on a rural small holding, this cute barn is completely detached, set apart from the owners' farmhouse and is only a short drive from the nearby village of Stithians and an even shorter drive to the local pub. The large open plan living space has patio doors that open onto a private garden with stunning views across the surrounding countryside, where the owners' flock of sheep can sometimes be seen grazing.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The light bedroom and en suite bathroom are up three steps, here you can sit in bed with your morning tea looking out at the views.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Babes in arms up to 12 months old are welcome at The Sheep Shed."/>
        <cottage position="48" type="C" code="1226" year="2025" name="The Haven" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.6073518" lon="-4.72400585" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/1226/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + cot" bedrooms="4" rent="Price per week £478 - £562" changeover="Saturday" town="Port Isaac" towndis="4.9 miles E of Port Isaac" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="478.04" maxRent="562.4" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="In the peaceful country hamlet of Trewalder, just a short drive from the wild cliffs and sandy beaches of the north Cornish coast and the fishing village of Port Isaac of 'Doc Martin' fame, The Haven is a delightful, immaculately presented, detached property with beamed ceilings downstairs and stripped pine doors in most rooms. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The spacious kitchen/diner is very well-equipped, and has doors that lead out to the sunny patio and large enclosed garden, which is ideal for young children. The sitting-room has soft, comfortable furnishings and a wood-burner effect electric stove set in a striking fireplace. Colourful linens and curtains complement the polished wood floors of the bedrooms, one of which is on the ground floor."/>
        <cottage position="49" type="C" code="4454" year="2025" name="The Boatshed" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.11026569" lon="-5.40285307" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4454/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £479 - £599" changeover="Friday" town="Praa Sands" towndis="Praa Sands" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="479.2003" maxRent="599.0004" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Wow! This beautifully appointed former boatshed is stunning, with reverse level living making the most of the wonderful views and, of course, the sunsets.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Set in a secluded spot at the end of a private lane surrounded by fields and with far reaching views to the sea, this gorgeous getaway is perfect for a relaxing break as it is set apart from the owners' cottage, while they are close enough to provide advice on local cafes, restaurants and other amenities (kayak/SUP hire, surfing, boat trips to name but a few).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Cross your private south-facing terrace and enter the kitchen/dining-area. The bedroom is also on this ground floor level; accessed via a fantastic industrial sliding door, made with original Georgian timbers, and ta-dah here's your comfortable king-size bed. Slip in between the luxury cotton sheets and…sweet dreams… The shower-room on the ground floor is equally as fabulous, with a double walk-in shower and unique Scandinavian towel rail and stone wash-basin.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Nordic style is synonymous to The Boatshed, every thought has gone into making this abode unique and styled with flair. The sitting-room on the first floor has a floor to ceiling, west-facing window; the sunsets are stunning and with a fabulous contemporary fire you can snuggle up in the warmth. No curtains are necessary in this first floor room as you are not overlooked and the light floods in. Take in the lovely views, there's even a distant sea view towards Prussia Cove and on a clear day Mount's Bay too. At night enjoy the clear west Cornwall skies and occasionally the Milky Way.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Set within the grounds of the owners' home, close to the coast, The Boatshed is perfect for guests looking to explore the South West Coast Path or bathers who prefer quiet coves for swimming. Leave your car as there is a footpath from your doorstep to Kenneggy Cove, if you head east you will reach Praa Sands and, further on, Rinsey. Head west and you will pass Prussia Cove; if you fancy a good stomp, carry on past Cudden Point to Marazion and St Michael's Mount.">
            <specialOffers>
                <specialOffer title="Special Offer - 20% off" dates="1 Nov 2025 to 15 Nov 2025" priceFull="Full Rent £599.00" priceNow="Now £479.20"/>
            </specialOffers>
        </cottage>
        <cottage position="50" type="C" code="5872" year="2025" name="7 Chapel Street" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.08229808" lon="-5.53969502" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5872/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 3 + cot" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £484 - £510" changeover="Friday" town="Mousehole" towndis="Mousehole" location="" maxAdults="3" minRent="484.367" maxRent="509.86" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Tucked away in the heart of the historic fishing village of Mousehole, 7 Chapel Street is a sweet two bedroom cottage offering a perfect coastal escape. Brimming with charm, the cottage sits on one of the village's enchanting, cobbled streets, still walked by fishermen and once whispered through by smugglers of old. Just a minute's stroll leads you to the picture perfect harbour where morning swims in calm waters are a beloved ritual. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The owner, Steve Deeks, an established racing driver who has coached and mentored FI champions, became enchanted with the village and its stories from the sailors and fishermen and set up this delightful home surrounded by the light and energy he loves about the village. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Step inside to find a welcoming open plan living and dining area thoughtfully designed to make the most of the cosy space giving a relaxed coastal feel. A huge wood-burner sits proudly in the heart of the room, radiating warmth hrough the whole cottage on chillier evenings, sink back into the sofas and curl up with a book or share your day's adventures over a glass of wine. The kitchen is a delightful mix of charm and practicality. Whether cooking up a hearty breakfast or a romantic supper, this kitchen is a social space which invites you to cook with ease.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;A king-size bedroom on this floor offers a restful retreat with luxurious linens and down the stairs the lower ground floor reveals a sweet single bedroom and family bathroom complete with a bath and fitted overhead shower, ideal after a day exploring the Cornish coastline.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside, a shared courtyard with bistro-style table and chairs provides a sunny spot to sit back and unwind with a glass of something chilled. A friendly pub lies just a stone's throw away and an excellent delicatessen is just around the corner, pick up your picnic treats and head to the beach for the day. For an unforgettable dining experience, be sure to book at a table at the renowned 2 Duke Street where celebrated chefs serve up exquisite seasonal dishes using the finest local produce in a relaxed and stylish setting. This cottage is a place to slow down, breathe in the sea air and soak up the timeless magic of Mousehole.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Parking is in one of the public car parks in the village approximately 200 yards from the property."/>
        <cottage position="51" type="C" code="4516" year="2025" name="Willow Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.13181371" lon="-5.16039312" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4516/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £487" changeover="Friday" town="Helford" towndis="2.9 miles N of Helford" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="487.2" maxRent="487.2" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="**£100 off any week-long booking between 31st October 2025 - 5th December 2025. Please use code SALE100 when booking.**&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This idyllic hideaway is set in a tranquil country location, nestled in the owners' smallholding, in the romantic Helford area. Willow Cottage is a beautiful retreat for two (and your four-legged friend) and is ideal for both a relaxing week or weekend getaway. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;There is plenty of space but it is ever so cosy. The minute you enter through the entrance hall into the beautifully furnished open plan living space with its charming wood-burner and high ceilings you will feel right at home. Willow Cottage has been thoughtfully designed for comfortable living; the large kitchen has a splendid island for food prep or where your loved one can perch with a glass of wine while supper is being prepared, even the views from the kitchen sink overlooking wooded valleys are to die for. The large sofa is perfect for snuggling up together; a perfect place to enjoy a hot cup of coffee from the Nespresso machine or perhaps relaxing with a good book in front of the wood-burner. The sitting area opens up to a lovely patio just for you, hide away from the world with only the owners' back garden and the birds nearby. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The fabulous bedroom has luxurious crisp sheets where you will drift off into a peaceful slumber. The bathroom has a wonderful roll-top bath for two - immerse yourself in the bubbles and let your aches and pains ebb away in the tub or if you prefer a shower there is a large shower to soak yourself under. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Tucked away down a private lane, this gorgeous rural property shares its location with the owners and [Cuddle Cabin (3959)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-3959.html &quot;Cuddle Cabin&quot;) however there is plenty of space from one another. "/>
        <cottage position="52" type="C" code="4194" year="2025" name="Lowenna" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.0172811" lon="-5.09645462" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4194/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £488 - £495" changeover="Friday" town="Coverack" towndis="Coverack" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="487.62" maxRent="495.144" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Perched on the stunning Coverack Headland, Lowenna is a charming and elegant second-floor apartment situated in one of the most gorgeous locations within the Lizard Peninsula.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The name &quot;Lowenna&quot; means joy, happiness and bliss in Cornish, which sums up exactly how you'll feel staying here.&#xD;&#xA;Step straight onto the South West Coast Path from the private communal gardens, where scenic cliffside walks lead to a beautiful sandy cove. The apartment sits within the grounds of the former Headland Hotel, giving guests access to peaceful surroundings with stunning oceanic views, a tennis court, and woodland to explore. Mears Beach is a short walk away. Please note, Lowenna is on the second floor, there's no lift.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Inside, the open plan living space is bright and airy, offering a real sense of calm, the moment you walk in. Large windows let lots of beautiful light in, making it the perfect spot to unwind. After a day of exploring, sink into the Chesterfield sofa with a glass of wine, after rustling up some holiday treats in the well-equipped kitchen and do bring along your Fire Stick for streaming your favourite TV programme if you can draw yourself away from the wonderful sea views.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The king-size bedroom is decorated in soft, calming tones and offers glimpses of the sea, a dreamy setting for a romantic break. Across the hall, the modern bathroom has a lovely deep bath, perfect for a long soak after a day out swimming in the Atlantic, bird watching, hiking or diving!"/>
        <cottage position="53" type="C" code="3803" year="2025" name="Trelowth Chapel" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.32322829" lon="-4.82749416" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3803/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4 + cot" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £488 - £543" changeover="Friday" town="Mevagissey" towndis="4.2 miles NW of Mevagissey" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="488.2977" maxRent="542.553" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Close to the picturesque fishing harbour at Mevagissey and the wonders of Heligan Gardens, this utterly delightful semi-detached chapel conversion is a wonderful example of thoughtful and skilled craftmanship. Attention to detail is evident at every turn, all topped off by superb quality fittings and furnishings offering every comfort you could wish. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The impressive living space on the ground floor, filled with light from soaring arched windows, accesses an inner hallway with a big family bathroom and thickly-carpeted stairs which lead up to the en suite bedroom and twin bedroom above. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;A paved courtyard outside is sheltered by high fences and provides the ideal place for a morning coffee or evening meal on warm summer days. Set on the edge of a small village and with beaches, fishing harbours and coastal footpaths just a couple of miles away, this is the perfect holiday location."/>
        <cottage position="54" type="C" code="4704" year="2025" name="Potters Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.08313" lon="-5.53996" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4704/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 5 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £490 - £544" changeover="Saturday" town="Mousehole" towndis="Mousehole" location="" maxAdults="5" minRent="489.51" maxRent="543.9" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="In the heart of Mousehole and within walking distance from the bustling harbour, this stunning dog-friendly cottage is simply charming and offers a wonderful seaside escape. Potters Cottage is tucked away in a secluded spot (shared with two other cottages) reached via a little cobbled lane.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Elegantly furnished Potters Cottage is a gorgeous retreat, perfect for a family, two couples or an intimate love nest for two. Once an old Pilchard Press, it has recently been lovingly refurbished to offer a chic and cosy bolthole for five lucky guests. Two traditional granite steps lead down to the characterful stable-door and straight into the impressive open plan living area which is packed with features. Sink into the cosy sofas and instantly switch off from the stresses and strains of everyday life. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The kitchen is well-equipped with everything you need to create those fabulous holiday breakfasts or lazy evening suppers. Plan your days out whilst gathering to enjoy delicious food; the stable-door can be opened wide on balmy summer evenings if you fancy a spot of al fresco dining in the sunshine. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Heading up the super-snug stairs you will find two double bedrooms and a single bedroom, all furnished with wonderfully comfy beds, crisp white linens, heritage radiators, lovely throws and plentiful cushions - you are guaranteed a relaxing night's slumber at Potters Cottage. The contemporary family bathroom is also located on this floor, with a bath and fitted shower.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside the property there is a shared courtyard area, where you can enjoy a spot of lunch in the sunshine or a cocktail before heading into Mousehole for a bite to eat.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Potters Cottage is a wonderful blend of old and new with all mod-cons taken care of within the stylish interior."/>
        <cottage position="55" type="C" code="5667" year="2025" name="River View Terrace" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.361470437" lon="-4.6408447419" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5667/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £490 - £612" changeover="Saturday" town="Fowey" towndis="1.8 miles N of Fowey" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="489.6" maxRent="612" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Come and treat yourself to a wonderful holiday in the peaceful creekside village of Golant on the banks of the River Fowey. With the most gorgeous views of the tidal waters over to the ancient woodland beyond that will have you mesmerised from the minute you arrive, River View Terrace certainly lives up to its name. It's a water lover's paradise and a fabulous year-round retreat to explore what has to be one of the prettiest parts of Cornwall.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Spend your days kayaking and paddle-boarding up the river, strolling along the riverbanks through ancient woodland, soaking up the sailing scene in nearby Fowey or simply kicking back on the terrace drinking in those glorious views. Holidays don't get don't much better than this.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Enjoying a prime elevated position, this mid-terrace retreat, has cosy and comfortable interiors creating a delightful home-from-home atmosphere. The living accommodation sits on the ground floor and the large bay window in the sitting-room perfectly frames the marvellous views, so if the weather is a little temperamental you can seek refuge inside and still enjoy the wonderful surroundings. Conjure up culinary delights with the best local produce in the kitchen/dining-room, best served up in the terraced garden with those breathtaking views creating the perfect backdrop. There are three bedrooms set over two floors, each floor having its own bathing facilities, offering a degree of privacy. Lazy holiday lie-ins will definitely be the order of the day in bedroom one, as waking up to that view will make it difficult to get out of bed, so breakfast in bed is a must!&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Please be advised that due to its charming village location, access to Golant and River View Terrace is narrow, when accessing the property there is a steep hill with a narrow section between two granite posts (7.5ft width).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Although children under 8 are regrettably not accepted at this property, babies up to six months are welcome."/>
        <cottage position="56" type="C" code="5129" year="2025" name="Guillemot" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.1456827884" lon="-5.06741790964" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5129/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £493" changeover="Saturday" town="Falmouth" towndis="Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="492.9" maxRent="492.9" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Just a stone's throw from beautiful Gyllyngvase beach and its renowned cafe/restaurant and a short stroll away from the delights of Falmouth town, Guillemot is a fantastic choice for a fun-filled, coastal holiday. Perfect for two (and your little dog), this charming retreat has been thoughtfully furnished - allowing you to slip into holiday mode as soon as you arrive. Its location is rather special too, ideal for coast path adventures, trying out kayaking, canoeing or a windsurfing lesson from the beach, or simply enjoying a restful escape by the sea.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Guillemot is adjoined to the owners' house but has plenty of privacy and is accessed via your own private front door. The entrance hall leads to the light-filled, open plan living space, where you will find the stylish kitchen - well-equipped with high quality appliances, including a Bosch coffee machine. Perfect for your morning coffee! Perch at the breakfast-bar and enjoy a leisurely breakfast before you head out for the day's adventures, and if you wish to relax for a little while, the living area has a comfortable sofa and a Smart TV.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The king-size bedroom is decorated in beautifully bright colours, perfectly complementing your coastal location. Here you'll find a TV, plenty of storage space and an en suite shower-room to wash off sandy toes at the end of the day. Outside, there is a lovely, enclosed courtyard at the front of the property - just the spot for a sundowner after strolling back from the beach."/>
        <cottage position="57" type="C" code="4298" year="2025" name="Tree Tops Cabin" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="49.98910443" lon="-5.1800108" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4298/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £493" changeover="Friday" town="Cadgwith" towndis="Cadgwith" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="492.9795" maxRent="492.9795" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Looking for the perfect get-away-from-it-all retreat? Look no further! Tree Tops Cabin is that and so much more, sat high up in the trees with a peaceful stream trickling through below, it has a real rural feel yet is only a few hundred yards from the sea, beach and friendly local pub in the idyllic Cornish fishing village of Cadgwith. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Step inside and you will immediately feel at home, every single detail has been thoughtfully put together and provided, with a calming colour scheme of soft greys and whites. This true hideaway has everything you could need for a comfortable break away from the everyday, complete with super-comfy king-size bed (facing the floor-to-ceiling windows, so you can enjoy a morning cuppa in bed whilst taking in the view - bliss!), snuggly sofa and toasty wood-burner (ensuring cosiness out-of-season). There's also a delightful kitchen-area tucked away at the far end of the cabin, featuring a mini oven with two-ring hob, fridge, kettle and toaster, sweet dining-area, where you can enjoy a scrumptious supper whilst also taking in the relaxing view, and, last but not least, stylish shower-room.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside, the raised deck provides the ideal place to sit back, relax (perhaps with a good book and a glass of your favourite tipple), take in the fresh air and enjoy the tranquil treetop view, all with the calming sound of the stream below and birds chirping nearby. Why not dine al fresco of an evening or, if you don't feel like cooking, head to the welcoming local pub, serving delicious locally-sourced food including fresh seafood sourced from the cove, just a short walk away. The friendly but unobtrusive owners live in the neighbouring cottage, so are on-hand if you need a local's advice or have any questions. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Arguably the most picturesque village on the Lizard peninsula and still a thriving fishing community, friendly Cadgwith also boasts a restaurant, gift and craft shop and freshly caught fish for sale right on the cove. Nearby Ruan Minor has a handy convenience shop as well as the Treleague Dairy farm shop, where you can buy their locally-sourced produce including clotted cream, eggs and fresh milk. You may never want to leave this lovely place, however, if you can bear to tear yourselves away, there is plenty to see and do within easy reach. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;If you want to explore by foot, the South West Coast Path, along the dramatic coastline with breathtaking coastal views, is right on your doorstep. For beach days, Kennack Sands (a designated Area of Outstanding Natural Beauty) is just a couple of miles away - well-known amongst the surfing community for its good-sized waves and great for walking your four-legged friend too (the east side is dog-friendly all year-round). &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Within a short drive are picturesque Kynance Cove, the village of Mullion (with its old smugglers' coves, local shops, pubs and restaurants), Poldhu Cove (the place to stop for a luxury hot chocolate!), the Lizard (where you can enjoy folk music, sea shanties or jazz at the local pub) and the picturesque Helford River. If you fancy giving some water sports a try, surfing, kayaking, paddle-boarding and windsurfing are all available locally too (if you want to bring your own kayaks, surfboards, bikes etc these can be stored under the cabin). &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;All in all, Tree Tops Cabin provides a place where you can relax, recharge and enjoy some quality time together in one of the most beautiful parts of Cornwall. "/>
        <cottage position="58" type="C" code="5051" year="2025" name="3 Harbour Court" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.17974948" lon="-4.97505248" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5051/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £493" changeover="Friday" town="Portscatho" towndis="Portscatho" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="493" maxRent="493" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Welcome to 3 Harbour Court, a stylish bijou first floor apartment perfectly placed in the beating heart of Portscatho village and just a stone's throw from the pretty harbour, scenic coast path and stunning beaches of the Roseland peninsula.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Portscatho has all you need for the perfect holiday and 3 Harbour Court has everything virtually on the doorstep. With a lovely selection of traditional village shops, eateries and cafes you may never need to take your car out but if you do decide to travel further afield the delights of Cornwall await.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Conveniently tucked away off the main street in Portscatho, 3 Harbour Court can be found just behind the harbour. Tatams, which serves freshly brewed coffee alongside a great selection of gorgeous pastries, can be found just around the corner on the harbour wall (the perfect start to the day), and Tide &amp; Thyme - a cafe and takeaway is just next door so that's breakfast, lunch and dinner all taken care of and just moments away! &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Access is shared with one other apartment with key entry to the door at the bottom of the stairs which split at the top. The left-hand staircase leads to 3 Harbour Court and the door leads into the open plan living area. Light, bright and welcoming, the stylish interior has been cleverly designed to make the most of the space and those memorising sea views. The sitting-area has a comfy sofa and armchair, perfect for gazing out to sea. A breakfast-bar sits in-between the sitting-area and kitchen, making the most of the views and giving you a bird's eye view over the roof tops to the harbour. The kitchen has all the equipment you will need to whip up a holiday meal and of course the dishwasher will take care of the washing up! &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside the kitchen a door leads onto a small balcony with just enough space for two. This little spot is the perfect place to sit and drink in the view or perhaps catch up on some holiday reading to the sound of the sea gently lapping against the seawall. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The bedroom is delightful, decorated in whites and blues - a nod to the nautical location. White plantation shutters give this room a Mediterranean vibe and a great night's sleep is assured in the super-king size bed. The shower-room is perfect after a busy day out and about. Parking is available in the village square but there are time restrictions, so it is recommended that you park a short walk away in New Road pay and display car park.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Whether you are looking for a romantic bolthole or simply looking for some time out in a quaint Cornish village, 3 Harbour Court has all the ingredients for the perfect getaway."/>
        <cottage position="59" type="C" code="1859" year="2025" name="Oyster Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.26961412" lon="-4.78908852" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/1859/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £501 - £589" changeover="Saturday" town="Mevagissey" towndis="Mevagissey" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="500.65" maxRent="589" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Oyster Cottage provides unexpectedly spacious and peaceful accommodation, tucked away from the hustle and bustle of Mevagissey's historic centre but just a three minute level walk from the harbourside. The end cottage of a modern terrace of five, there is a large, enclosed garden and private parking for a medium-sized car, an unexpected bonus in such a small village although beware of the narrow entrance. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This is a delightfully scenic village with narrow lanes of colourful terraced cottages crowding the hillsides around the sheltered harbour below. Fishermen still mend their nets on the harbourside and offer boat trips to visitors, and there are craft shops, tea-rooms and old smugglers' pubs to explore on dry land. Having negotiated the narrow winding streets, Oyster Cottage is a lovely holiday destination."/>
        <cottage position="60" type="C" code="5169" year="2025" name="Fisherton Cottage at Poughill" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.8418196600256" lon="-4.52738087457546" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5169/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 5 + 2 cots" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £501 - £557" changeover="Saturday" town="Bude" towndis="1.1 miles NE of Bude" location="" maxAdults="5" minRent="500.85" maxRent="556.5" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Situated in the pretty village of Poughill, on the road to Northcott Mouth Beach, you will find this delightful holiday abode. Perfectly placed for the fabulous beaches of Bude, with the quaint fishing villages of Boscastle and Port Isaac just a short drive away and a pub in the village, you really have found the perfect holiday cottage, you can even walk to Crooklets beach with your four-legged friend or venture to the shops all being 30 minutes away by foot.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;With oodles of charm and character, you will feel instantly at home from the moment you arrive here. The ground floor is home to a cosy sitting-room, where you will find a warming wood-burner for cooler months and a comfy sofa where you can snuggle up in front of the Smart TV. The separate dining-room has traditional slate floors and a fabulous original ornamental range, which wouldn't look out of place in Downton Abbey! Throughout the house you will find some gorgeous pieces of traditional furniture, like the dresser complete with pretty crockery and the beautiful, tiled floor in the hallway. In the kitchen you will find all the equipment you'll need to cook a holiday meal, including the all-important dishwasher and access to the garden, where you can wander out and enjoy your morning cuppa in the fresh air or enjoy a perfect sundowner after a day of holiday fun.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Climb the stairs and you will find three pretty bedrooms and the family bathroom. Bedroom one has a lovely outlook and with 'zip and link' beds, gives you the luxury to choose either a super-king double bed or twins. Bedroom two is a double bedroom overlooking the back garden and bedroom three has a single bed, ideal for either a child or adult. The family bathroom on the first floor has a bath with shower over. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Outside, a pretty cottage garden awaits, perfect for al fresco dining in the Cornish sunshine and of course your four-legged friend can join you too. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Being a traditional terraced Cornish cottage, the free village car park can be found 100 yards from the front door, however, on arrival you can pull in just past the row of cottages and unload your suitcases."/>
        <cottage position="61" type="C" code="4396" year="2025" name="Mount Wise Farmhouse" xcode="232" brandCode="" lat="50.17235506" lon="-5.21026575" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4396/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £505 - £722" changeover="Friday" town="Falmouth" towndis="6.5 miles W of Falmouth" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="505.3314" maxRent="721.902" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="Nestled in the heart of Cornwall, this remarkable 400 year old farmhouse is more than just a holiday cottage, it's an experience. From the moment you arrive, you're greeted by the enchanting beauty of its lovingly tended garden, which provides the perfect backdrop for your stay. The real welcome begins when you step inside, where the owner's exceptional homemade bread and cake await, together with very thoughtful welcome treats and surprises to make you feel instantly at home. Accommodating six lucky guests (but offering a reduction at certain times of year for smaller parties) and two, four-legged friends are most welcome too. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;At the heart of this home is a kitchen that any food lover would envy. So practical in its design and quality, it features a twin-oven electric Rangemaster, honed granite worktops, and a timeless double Belfast sink. Whether you're whipping up a simple breakfast or preparing a feast for family and friends, this space is designed to inspire. The large dining-table seats eight which is convenient if you are a larger party and it's the perfect space for gathering and sharing stories of the day's adventures. (You can also book neighbouring property [Mount Wise Cottage (2187)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-2187.html &quot;Mount Wise Cottage&quot;) that sleeps two, for even more family fun). **Why not book both properties together (sleeping 8 in total) for an extra special 2025 Christmas celebration and receive a festive 20% discount off each property.**&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The farmhouse's charm is evident in every corner, from its thick granite walls to its original fireplaces. The cosy sitting-room invites you to relax by the wood-burning stove, while the beautifully decorated bedrooms offer peaceful havens for restful nights. Each space has been thoughtfully arranged by the owner (who lives nearby) to balance historic character with modern comfort, creating a truly special place to unwind.">
            <specialOffers>
                <specialOffer title="Special Offer - 30% off" dates="31 Oct 2025 to 7 Nov 2025" priceFull="Full Rent from £577.60" priceNow="Now from £404.32"/>
                <specialOffer title="Special Offer - 30% off" dates="15 Nov 2025 to 22 Nov 2025" priceFull="Full Rent from £577.60" priceNow="Now from £404.32"/>
            </specialOffers>
        </cottage>
        <cottage position="62" type="C" code="4062" year="2025" name="Scenic Bay" xcode="167" brandCode="" lat="50.14429947" lon="-5.49823188" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4062/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £507 - £563" changeover="Friday" town="Penzance" towndis="2.4 miles NE of Penzance" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="506.8584" maxRent="563.176" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Scenic Bay is a dream, set in a spacious meadow with a stunning view to match its name. This pretty pod is beautifully finished and kitted out for all of your holiday needs. There is under-floor heating, making it wonderfully toasty whatever the time of year, and a heated towel rail too, ideal for drying those beach towels. The well-equipped kitchen area includes a sink, cooker, microwave, fridge and kettle, and there is even a TV provided - perfect for cosy nights in. The sofa, which converts with ease into a double bed, is the ideal spot for relaxing with a book or enjoying the view and there is a comfy double bed at the back of the pod too. The modern shower-room includes hot and cold running water and a proper flushing loo - luxury glamping at its best! &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Many an hour can be spent outside here too, enjoying quality time together in the picture-perfect surroundings - the panoramic vista runs from the Lizard peninsula in the east, with majestic St Michael's Mount in the middle to Mousehole in the west. Why not cook up a scrummy supper on the fire-pit barbecue and dine al fresco on the deck, drinking in the ever-changing view. Also snuggled into this spacious meadow are [Coastal Gaze](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-4063.html &quot;Coastal Gaze&quot;) and [Mount Lookout](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-4064.html &quot;Mount Lookout&quot;) - Scenic Bay is the first of the three and each have their own private areas."/>
        <cottage position="63" type="C" code="4063" year="2025" name="Coastal Gaze" xcode="167" brandCode="" lat="50.14433386" lon="-5.49853229" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4063/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £507 - £563" changeover="Friday" town="Penzance" towndis="2.4 miles NE of Penzance" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="506.8584" maxRent="563.176" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="This beautifully situated pod has outstanding 180 degree views across Mount's Bay, running from the Lizard peninsula in the east, with majestic St Michael's Mount in the middle to Mousehole in the west. Coastal Gaze is a special retreat that you will want to return to time and time again. Wonderfully styled inside, every detail and item has been thoughtfully put together and provided. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The well-equipped kitchen area is complete with a cooker, microwave, fridge and kettle (cuppa, anyone?), and there is even a TV - ideal for cosy nights in. The cleverly-designed sofa converts to a double bed with ease and there is a comfy double bed at the back of the pod too. The under-floor heating will keep you toasty whatever the weather and there is, of course, a stylish en suite shower-room complete with hot and cold running water, flushing loo and heated towel rail. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;But that's not all, outside you can snooze in the sun, dine al fresco on the deck, cook up a storm (or toast some marshmallows!) on the fire-pit barbecue until your heart's content. Also snuggled into this spacious meadow are [Scenic Bay](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-4062.html &quot;Scenic Bay&quot;) and [Mount Lookout](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-4064.html &quot;Mount Lookout&quot;) - Coastal Gaze is the middle of the three and each have their own private areas."/>
        <cottage position="64" type="C" code="5278" year="2025" name="The Pilchard Shed" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.15876567" lon="-5.01502275" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5278/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per night £73 - £115" changeover="Saturday" town="St Mawes" towndis="St Mawes" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="73.04176" maxRent="114.5745" rentPeriod="Daily" maxPets="0" introText="Just a stone's throw away from the vibrant harbourside in the magical Roseland village of St Mawes, The Pilchard Shed is an oh so cute hideaway, tucked up a cobbled pathway and perfect for a romantic getaway or a solo retreat. From the moment you arrive on the Roseland Peninsula you will feel yourself relax into your holiday. Beautiful countryside and wooded valleys offer glimpses of the sea which culminate in a panoramic seascape when you arrive in charming St Mawes. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The Pilchard Shed could not be more centrally located, up a tiny, cobbled alley from the harbour. This gorgeous bijou abode has been cleverly crafted to optimise the small but perfectly formed space and from the moment you arrive you will be captivated. The cosy seating has a seaside theme, beautifully furnished in blue hues to match the location. A dining-table folds away and hangs on the wall when you don't need it, optimising the living space. Above the built-in seating, a gorgeous king-size cabin bed awaits up a ladder (please take care and mind your head) and the clever use of space continues with built in cupboards underneath.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The tiny galley kitchen packs a big punch with a combination microwave and fridge with small freezer compartment, perfect for ice cubes for your evening aperitif! The shower-room is through the kitchen, beautifully finished with fabulous mosaic tiles. Whilst there is no TV or outside space at The Pilchard Shed, the colourful harbourside is just moments away, so why not take your morning coffee or evening aperitif down the cobbled footpath and sit by the water's edge to watch the boats sail by, the perfect dreamy holiday pastime!&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;For larger parties or groups of friends why not book neighbouring [Manor Cottage (4988)]( https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-4988.html &quot;Manor Cottage&quot;) alongside The Pilchard Shed."/>
        <cottage position="65" type="C" code="4229" year="2025" name="Puffin" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.42388935" lon="-5.06228864" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4229/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + 2 cots" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £515 - £644" changeover="Friday" town="Newquay" towndis="1.2 miles NE of Newquay" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="515.28" maxRent="644.1" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="Set on the cliffs surrounding stunning coastline, Puffin is found at the centre of the cluster of houses on the headland in the foreground which sits between the beaches of Porth and Lusty Glaze. Enjoy listening to the crashing waves on the shore as you sip a drink on the balcony of this mid-terraced house or wander over the headland to watch the most fabulous sunsets.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Opening the front door to the entrance hall you are greeted by a light and bright property; take the stairs up to the open plan living space which is subtly furnished in coastal soft greys and yellows. You can enjoy glimpses of the sea from the sitting-area window and keep the windows open and listen to the crashing waves. The large sofas are perfect for you all to kick back and relax together after a day on the beach, remember to bring your login details for streaming services on the Smart TV. The dining-area looks out to the private balcony where you can sit in the sun with your morning coffee and admire the view. The kitchen is compact, however equipped to a good standard with all you may need to cook up something rather special.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Take the stairs down to the ground floor; here you will find three double bedrooms and family shower-room along with access to the outside area. The principal bedroom has a comfy double bed and of course a fabulous en suite shower-room along with patio doors that open to your private decked area and shared grassy lawn. Bedroom two has 'zip and link' beds to provide flexibility for your party and an extra child can be accommodated on a fold out bed. This bedroom also has patio doors leading onto a decked area. Bedroom three is tucked away at the back of the house and has a lovely double bed, there is a family shower-room on this floor too. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The outside space at Puffin is lovely, you have a private balcony on the first floor with side views down to the beach where you can enjoy the sunshine and a coffee. If you want space for everyone to be together enjoy your own decked area with a picnic bench which leads to the shared lawn area which is shared by the properties in the row with lovely sea views and perfect for the dog to have a run around or the kids to kick a football. Puffin boasts its own private mid tide access to Porth Beach and just a moment’s stroll from the popular Lusty Glaze beach with its fabulous restaurant.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Puffin is situated within the grounds of the Glendorgal Hotel, with around 17 acres of private (and gated) headland. This attractive property sits in a quiet cul-de-sac of purpose-built holiday homes."/>
        <cottage position="66" type="C" code="5274" year="2025" name="Pedney" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.106742" lon="-5.572354" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5274/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per night £74 - £124" changeover="Friday" town="Mousehole" towndis="2.2 miles NW of Mousehole" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="73.77728" maxRent="124.192" rentPeriod="Daily" maxPets="1" introText="Hidden away in a sweet hamlet in magical far west Cornwall, Pedney is an idyllic, dog-friendly shepherd's hut for two. If you're looking to escape to a tranquil hideaway, within easy reach of the beautiful Cornish coastline, this is just the place…&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Tucked away amongst a subtropical garden, Pedney's wonderfully rustic interiors are sure to charm you. The beautiful hand-crafted kitchen comes complete with all the essentials for rustling up simple meals, with a wooden dining table and chairs, cosy wood-burner and a sweet seating area. At the other end of the hut, you'll find a sumptuous double bed, ideal for those leisurely lie ins, and stylish en suite shower-room. Pedney's blissful, laid-back vibe invites you to leave your worries behind and relax for a little while - you're on holiday after all!&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;With its delightful sub-tropical plants and flowers, the serene and secluded outside space is the perfect spot too for blissful days unwinding under the Cornish sunshine. There are two cute outdoor seating areas here, ideal for lazy al fresco breakfasts or an evening tipple after a day spent exploring the coastline. "/>
        <cottage position="67" type="C" code="4973" year="2025" name="Porth Chapel Cabin" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.106742" lon="-5.572354" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4973/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per night £74 - £124" changeover="Friday" town="Mousehole" towndis="2.2 miles NW of Mousehole" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="73.77728" maxRent="124.192" rentPeriod="Daily" maxPets="1" introText="Far West Cornwall is renowned for its glorious golden sandy beaches, hidden coves and idyllic countryside, stretching as far as the eye can see. Porth Chapel Cabin is an enchanting romantic bolthole, hidden away in a sub-tropical paradise and just a short journey away from the delights of St Ives and Mousehole.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Deep in the beating heart of west Cornwall, Porth Chapel Cabin is a beautifully crafted retreat with a gorgeous outside terrace where you can sit in the Cornish sun from dawn until dusk. Inside the open plan cabin is simply stunning. Contemporary lighting, a brilliant sound system and a Smart TV, marry seamlessly with quirky interiors where exposed brick and oak add charm and character.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The kitchen has been cleverly handcrafted, using upcycled materials. There's everything you need to whip up delicious holiday treats, so shop in one of many local farm shops and roadside stalls for the freshest of Cornish produce. Snuggle up in front of the wood-burner, perfect whatever the weather, this really is the location for all seasons.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The dreamy bed with feature brass bedstead has luxury linens, so sweet dreams are assured. The shower-room is perfect for a refreshing shower after a busy day out and about exploring the local area. Outside, the large decked space has the perfect combination of two seating areas and a dining-table so you can follow the sun or sit in the shade on a hot day. The barbecue invites you to dine al fresco surrounded by magical sub-tropical trees, paradise indeed! Porth Chapel Cabin...where your Cornish fairy-tale awaits.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;There is another hideaway on site [Poldhu (4976)]( https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-4976.html &quot;Poldhu&quot;) and [Beryas Cottage (4970)]( https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-4970.html &quot;Beryas Cottage&quot;), but please note the properties are positioned in a way so you have plenty of privacy."/>
        <cottage position="68" type="C" code="5143" year="2025" name="Little Lesquite" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.430873" lon="-4.7228475" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5143/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per night £74 - £107" changeover="Friday" town="Lostwithiel" towndis="2.9 miles NW of Lostwithiel" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="74.13368" maxRent="106.9695" rentPeriod="Daily" maxPets="0" introText="Pack up a bag, grab your loved one and whisk them off for a magical break away at the wonderful world of Little Lesquite! Tucked away along a country lane, with a stunning outdoor bathtub for two for under the stars bathing, miles of country rambles right on your doorstep, birds and wildlife to entertain you throughout the day (binoculars at the ready) and taking centre stage, the most gorgeous views stretching out across open countryside to the nature reserve and wildly dramatic Helman Tor. This rural idyll is the ultimate retreat for laid back lovers to soak up the great outdoors. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Whether you are lounging in the bath, bubbles of either variety optional, enjoying elevenses perched on the steps or barbecuing over the fire-pit watching the sunset at the end of a perfect day in Cornwall, relax kick back, take in that view and revitalise your senses. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Step inside and this charming shepherd's hut has been exquisitely deigned by the lovely owners who along with their dear little dog, are on hand to give you a very warm welcome and then leave you in peace to enjoy every moment of your time at Little Lesquite. Comfort and romance were surely at the top of the list with the sumptuous king-sized bed, adorned with luscious linens ensuring that lazy holiday lie ins are a must. When you are ready to cook up breakfast, the handmade kitchen comes complete with a 2 ring induction hob, electric oven, fridge, toaster, kettle and even a coffee machine - what more do you need. If you can't be tempted to eat outside, you can dine inside around the little dining-table which can be folded away when you want a little more space. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Perfect for summertime escapes and thanks to that all important wood-burner, making it even cosier on long lazy winter breaks, Little Lesquite is the perfect tonic all year round."/>
        <cottage position="69" type="C" code="3966" year="2025" name="Chyandour" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.18211862" lon="-5.01008204" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3966/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £521 - £651" changeover="Friday" town="St Mawes" towndis="1.7 miles N of St Mawes" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="520.8" maxRent="651" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="There are fabulous views over the sailing waters around St Mawes from both the garden and first floor living-room of this contemporary eco-house, set on the edge of St Just in Roseland on the beautiful Roseland peninsula. Looking out over green fields to the sea beyond, the wonderful sight of yachts clustering on the water in summer races and frothing waves in winter winds will prove fascinating to watch and guaranteed to delight. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Unassuming from the approach road, Chyandour looks part of a terrace of small Victorian cottages but once you’ve turned downhill and into the quiet cul-de-sac at the rear of the terrace you see the unexpected sight of a row of tall, timber-clad modern houses with peaked apex rooflines and glass-fronted balconies. Big rooms, high ceilings and an open plan living area make this a wonderfully hospitable holiday home, perfect for families and couples alike. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;There are delightful creekside and coastal walks nearby, beaches galore and the iconic sailing town of St Mawes, with its fabulous restaurants, shops and galleries, just a five minute drive away.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Steps lead up from the parking-area to a smooth green lawn bordered with colourful shrubs and a patio set with outdoor dining furniture and a barbecue, a wonderful spot for family feasts on mellow summer evenings."/>
        <cottage position="70" type="C" code="5830" year="2025" name="Roskennals Granary" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.12330273" lon="-5.59688805" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5830/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4 + cot" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £522 - £580" changeover="Saturday" town="Penzance" towndis="2.5 miles W of Penzance" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="522.018" maxRent="580.02" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="A private driveway leads you to this very special home, nestled amidst breathtaking gardens surrounded by woodland and a bordering stream, Roskennals Granary is a charming two bedroom reverse level cottage which exudes character and idyllic countryside living. Meticulously restored with much love by its current owners (who live on site) and with great attention to detail, this property offers a combination of serenity and natural beauty.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Being Grade II Listed, Roskennals Granary is brimming with history. Climb the original Cornish granite steps and enter the thoughtfully designed open plan layout which seamlessly integrates a bespoke kitchen with plenty of room to prepare a feast of Cornish produce. A spacious dining-area and a sitting-area with sumptuous sofas to sink into, the highlight here being the dramatic floor to ceiling window flooding the room with natural light and offering uninterrupted views of the magnificent gardens. This feature window creates a special connection between the interior and the outdoors enhancing the tranquil ambience. A sweet wood-burner fills the space with warmth during cooler evenings.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Downstairs are two delightful bedrooms, one a king with plush linens and elegant finishes and the second a sweet twin, both with delightful traditional cottage windows overlooking the gardens and grounds. A luxury shower-room boasts a high end finish and sits between the two bedrooms.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Surrounding this delightful property are lovingly maintained gardens, featuring a wildlife pond, peaceful stream and a diverse range of plants, creating a sanctuary for guests and has local wildlife in abundance. Take a breath and admire the visiting heron, kingfishers and darting dragonflies and a wandering deer looking for fallen fruits - do have your camera ready! Your canine friend is also welcome to enjoy the holiday too.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;This gorgeous home shares the beautiful surroundings with two other stunning cottages but seclusion and privacy are respected by the location of each one. Larger groups of friends or family could holiday together, &#xD;&#xA;[Roskennals Mill (5829)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-5829.html &quot;Roskennals Mill&quot;) sleeps five and [Ellas Pottery (5831)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-5831.html &quot;Ellas Pottery&quot;) sleeping two so why not join together and celebrate a special occasion/event in this wonderful setting?">
        </cottage>
        <cottage position="71" type="C" code="5213" year="2025" name="Bosun's Locker" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.15797864" lon="-5.0158596" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5213/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £527" changeover="Saturday" town="St Mawes" towndis="St Mawes" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="527.35" maxRent="527.35" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Welcome to Bosun's Locker, a hidden away apartment conveniently situated in the heart of the vibrant Roseland village of St Mawes and perfect for a car-free Cornish getaway for two.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;St Mawes has all you need for a great holiday with beaches, a bustling harbour, an eclectic range of shops and the coast path all literally on your doorstep. Bosun's Locker is hidden away off the harbour and reached through a shared access alleyway off the main street. Climb a series of steps to a small number of quiet, cloistered dwellings and you will reach the front elevation of Bosun's Locker with a pretty Mediterranean terrace complete with garden furniture and sun parasol to shelter you from the Cornish rays.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;All on one level, the interiors are cosy and welcoming. The living space has a sitting area, ideal for relaxing after a busy beach day and a separate breakfast-bar, perfect for two. The galley kitchen is small but perfectly formed and has all the equipment you'll need to cook a holiday meal. The comfy double bedroom is to the left of the living area, and the bathroom has a bath with a fitted shower overhead, so you can choose either a long soak or a refreshing shower. Bosun's Locker is a lovely bijou apartment, ideal for a couple looking for a Cornish getaway and perfectly situated close to all St Mawes has to offer."/>
        <cottage position="72" type="C" code="3132" year="2025" name="Bryher" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.18503237" lon="-4.97788992" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3132/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £533" changeover="Saturday" town="Portscatho" towndis="Portscatho" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="533" maxRent="533" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Bryher is a delightful barn conversion, semi-detached from [Lowenna (3133)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-3133.html &quot;Lowenna&quot;). The interior is contemporary, light and airy with solid wood flooring throughout and great attention to detail. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Located just a five minute walk from Porthcurnick Beach, with soft sand and rock pools galore, this is a wonderful location for a family holiday. A 10 minute stroll along the coastal footpath brings you to Portscatho, a pretty little harbourside village with its own sandy beach, a selection of shops and galleries, a couple of cafes and a popular pub. The shared orchard garden has fully enclosed lawns, lovely mature trees and sea views over the bay towards Nare Head and Gull Rock in one direction and rolling countryside in the other."/>
        <cottage position="73" type="C" code="4217" year="2025" name="Lake View" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.43724434" lon="-4.22715183" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4217/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + 2 cots" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £534 - £667" changeover="Saturday" town="Cargreen" towndis="Cargreen" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="533.6" maxRent="667" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="3" introText="Wind your way along country lanes to this idyllic haven, in the heart of the beautiful Tamar Valley, where you are sure to spend many an hour enjoying the wonderful views down to Kingsmill Lake, a tidal creek running down to the River Tamar. Set in a National Landscape (formerly known as an Area of Outstanding Natural beauty), this rural paradise is a superb location for wildlife enthusiasts, walkers and those who love peaceful countryside.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;It is furnished to a very high standard and extremely comfortable throughout, with vaulted ceilings, wooden floors, gorgeous bedrooms, stylish shower-rooms, a balcony to make the most of those far reaching views and a small private garden area offering a lovely setting for dining in the great outdoors. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The owners live on site and once they and their friendly dog Laika have given you a hearty greeting they will leave you to relax and enjoy your holiday. "/>
        <cottage position="74" type="C" code="5819" year="2025" name="Love Lane Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.11484865" lon="-5.55008293" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5819/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4 + 2 cots" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £537 - £596" changeover="Saturday" town="Penzance" towndis="Penzance" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="536.625" maxRent="596.2499" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="Nestled along a quiet rural lane in the seaside town of Penzance, Love Lane Cottage is a Grade II Listed property which exudes timeless charm and historical character. Dating back to 1675, this unique home is believed to be one of the oldest in Penzance. The cosy cottage retains much original appeal with features such as exposed beams, stone walls and an inviting ambiance that speaks of centuries of care and love. Inside this beautiful property, sleeping four, you'll discover charm and originality in equal balance. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;A fully equipped traditional kitchen with all the modern appliances installed, will provide the perfect opportunity to prepare a feast for the family. The dining-room has an original ornamental Rayburn that takes pride of place adding a nostalgic touch to this social space, a superb setting for memorable gatherings. Charming window seats in the sweet sitting-room allow you to sit back and warm yourself in front of the original granite fireplace with wood-burner.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Upstairs you will discover two delightful bedrooms steeped in vintage charm with carefully chosen furnishings and decor that complement the home's heritage. A single bathroom separates the two bedrooms, and overlooks the cottage's outstanding garden. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The gently sloping garden itself is a true highlight offering seclusion and bursting with mature shrubs, colourful summer flowers, a protected wildlife haven offering tranquility and nature at its finest. At the bottom of the garden is a meadow field closed off by the owners to carefully preserve and encourage visiting insects, a sanctuary for birds in the adjacent protected woodland and visiting dragonflies to the stream below. This cherished property is a piece of Cornish history providing a special retreat, yet is so very close to the sea and all that Penzance has to offer."/>
        <cottage position="75" type="C" code="4937" year="2025" name="Bokelly Cottage" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.55744002" lon="-4.76560786" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4937/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £539 - £673" changeover="Friday" town="Port Isaac" towndis="3.8 miles SE of Port Isaac" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="538.56" maxRent="673.2" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="As pretty as a picture and bursting with character, this idyllic retreat is waiting to welcome you to a very special holiday in north Cornwall. Set alongside the country road that leads to the little hamlet of Trelill, with gorgeous views stretching out across open countryside and glimpses of Bodmin Moor in the distance, you are only the shortest of drives to the very popular and truly stunning north Cornwall coastline.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;There's a treat in store with the beautifully styled interiors, which perfectly complement the gorgeous slate floors, exposed beams, chunky thick walls and feature fireplaces which add to the overall charm. Step over the threshold into the snug - a simply gorgeous space with the sweetest of wood-burners, inviting you to pull up a pew and relax from the moment you arrive. The living and dining space is divine, with calm and relaxing interiors, a cosy wood-burner and lots of beautiful touches throughout, and the country-style galley kitchen is perfect for preparing brunch or supper with fresh ingredients picked up from the local farm shop. The large garden and sunny terrace is the perfect spot to soak in that view whether enjoying a morning coffee before you head out for a day at the beach or an evening sundowner after that exhilarating surfing lesson. And we must mention the outside shower - ideal for washing off sandy toes and salty wetsuits after a day in the sea.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The bedrooms are sure to offer a peaceful night's sleep after a day of exploring this beautiful part of the world. All have stunning views over the garden and surrounding countryside and the main bedroom has the luxury of an en suite bathroom as well. Utter bliss! "/>
        <cottage position="76" type="C" code="3129" year="2025" name="Hayloft" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.1732613" lon="-4.97856914" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/3129/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2 + cot" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per week £541" changeover="Friday" town="Portscatho" towndis="Portscatho" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="540.8935" maxRent="540.8935" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="2" introText="This lovely stone-built barn is set back from an unspoilt country lane just outside the harbourside village of Gerrans. One of just two recently renovated barns ([Long Linhay (3142)](https://www.classic.co.uk/holiday-cottage/desc-3142.html &quot;Long Linhay&quot;) is nearby) Hayloft is the perfect retreat for couples who love exploring the beautiful Cornish coastline and countryside. A stroll across two fields leads to the coastal footpath, with the picturesque fishing village and harbour of Portscatho and its village store, art galleries, coffee shops and pub just a 15 minute walk away. There are plenty of places to eat out, with The Hidden Hut at Porthcurnick beach, wonderful restaurants at The Rosevine and Driftwood hotels and fine dining at The Idle Rocks and Hotel Tresanton in the renowned sailing town of St Mawes."/>
        <cottage position="77" type="C" code="4971" year="2025" name="The Bird Box" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.49844645" lon="-4.53649696" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/4971/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 2" bedrooms="1" rent="Price per night £78 - £121" changeover="Friday" town="Liskeard" towndis="4.6 miles NW of Liskeard" location="" maxAdults="2" minRent="78.25536" maxRent="120.768" rentPeriod="Daily" maxPets="1" introText="If you want to fly away from the everyday and immerse yourself in the very best that mother nature has to offer, then escape to this oh so special hideaway in the most magical of settings. Tucked away at the end of a country lane, this gorgeous bolthole is in an Area of Outstanding Natural Beauty and from the minute you arrive you'll understand why.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The surrounding countryside is stunning and the views mesmerising, and your own private garden is nothing short of paradise. You are sure to while away many an hour enjoying all the beauty that surrounds whether snuggled up in the comfy king-size bed, toasting marshmallows around the fire-pit or snoozing in the hammock. And your soundtrack for the day will be the birdsong - there's a reason it's called the Bird Box you know. From the beautiful dawn chorus in the morning to the enchanting hooting of the owls who provide the encore at the end of the day, these are the best form of tweets; they soothe the soul and lift the spirits - are you feeling relaxed yet?&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;For an extra treat there's an outside bath made for two - how romantic is that. Nestled next to a beautiful kiwi tree, the best time to enjoy a long soak is in the evening under the starry sky, it's an unforgettable sight.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Cool and laid-back interiors perfectly complement the setting. Wake up and fling open the cabin doors to soak up the serenity of your surroundings as you enjoy your morning coffee. Utter bliss! The kitchen has everything you might need for creating yummy holiday dishes, with a very sweet seating area for holiday breakfasts before a day of adventures. If the weather turns a little chilly, there is the cutest wood-burner ever to keep you warm and toasty - making it a lovely getaway any time of the year. There's no TV or WiFi here - why would you want it - so you are in for a digital detox and if you need help getting off to sleep it will be counting stars here, lying in bed looking out of the skygazing window above - dreamy….!&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Getting down to basics, in the neighbouring cabin you have a super shower to set you up for the day and that all -mportant eco-friendly compost toilet."/>
        <cottage position="78" type="C" code="5385" year="2025" name="Nare View" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.17824825" lon="-4.97883976" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5385/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £548 - £609" changeover="Friday" town="Portscatho" towndis="Portscatho" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="548.1" maxRent="609" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Portscatho is a much sought-after charming seaside village on the Roseland peninsula and Nare View is perfectly situated on Gerrans Hill, just moments away from stunning beaches and the vibrant harbourside. With far reaching views to the blue sea beyond, this beautifully presented Portscatho home may become one of your favourite places to stay. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Accommodating up to six guests in three bedrooms and decorated throughout in cool natural colours, Nare View has a warm welcome whichever time of year you choose to stay. When the sun is shining, when not on the beach or out and about exploring this beautiful part of the Cornish coast, you are likely to spend much of your time outside on the terrace. A real sun-trap in warm weather, so don't forget your hat! This is also the perfect spot for a tasty breakfast before you head out for your next adventure or when there is no need to rush, a leisurely lunch with friends or family.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Open up the French doors in the living-room and bring the outside into this relaxing space, snuggle up on the sofa in front of the wood-burner with a good book or take an afternoon nap after spending a lovely day on the beach. When hunger calls head into the stylish kitchen to rustle up a delicious dinner, there's an abundance of quality produce grown locally, just take a trip to the local farm shop and take your pick. If you prefer to let someone else do the cooking, book a table at one of the local eateries, they're all good, within walking distance and offer a friendly welcome.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;On the first floor choose from three lovely bedrooms, bedroom one has sea views from the bedroom window and a king-sized bed, The second bedroom, a twin room, is ideal for adults or children with full-size single beds. Bedroom three offers a cosy double bed (4'6&quot;), please note there is limited access down each side, and the bed may be more comfortably accessed from one side only. This bedroom may therefore be better suited to children or one guest. "/>
        <cottage position="79" type="C" code="2768" year="2025" name="76 Degrees Blue" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.02114282" lon="-5.09690225" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/2768/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 4" bedrooms="2" rent="Price per week £550 - £611" changeover="Sunday" town="Coverack" towndis="Coverack" location="" maxAdults="4" minRent="549.99" maxRent="611.1" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="0" introText="This light and spacious apartment with the most spectacular sea views could just be the perfect coastal retreat. Sitting on the Sunny Corner side of Coverack, above the pretty arc-shaped bay, 76 Degrees Blue is a great base from which to explore this stunning part of the Lizard peninsula.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;As you descend the 50 garden steps from the dedicated parking-area, (for those who prefer a flatter scenic walk avoiding the garden steps, there is alternative access to the ground floor via the coast path from the chapel), perhaps stop for a moment to take in the lovely blue colour of the sea. Continue further down one flight of internal stairs, through the attractive period building to the ground floor and you will find the entrance to this very well-kept apartment. Drop your bags, throw open the French doors and you will find the sheltered private garden, which boasts the most wonderful of sea views. This area is perfect for enjoying al fresco meals or just relaxing with a good book."/>
        <cottage position="80" type="C" code="5470" year="2025" name="The Rigging" xcode="0" brandCode="" lat="50.33609665" lon="-4.52428579" picURL="https://webpics.classic.co.uk/5470/list.jpg?w=236&amp;h=157&amp;mode=crop" accom="Sleeps 6 + cot" bedrooms="3" rent="Price per week £550 - £688" changeover="Friday" town="Polperro" towndis="Polperro" location="" maxAdults="6" minRent="550.16" maxRent="687.7" rentPeriod="Weekly" maxPets="1" introText="Come and live the coastal life at The Rigging, our most charming, white-washed cottage set in the idyllic harbourside village of Polperro. With bags of original features paired with modern day comforts, The Rigging is a haven for relaxation and a wonderful base to discover all the delights that this part of Cornwall has to offer.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Lovingly presented, the owners have created a home-from-home experience, where a warm welcome awaits. Pull into your parking area, a real bonus for Polperro, and step inside to discover your holiday haven. Set over three floors, The Rigging is deceptively spacious and surprisingly light for a traditional Cornish Cottage. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The cottage sitting-room is a calm space, accented in gentle shades to perfectly complement the setting and the kitchen/dining-room will be the place to gather for everything from holiday breakfasts, mid-morning snacks and leisurely suppers. On warmer days enjoy your meals on the sunny terrace at the front of the cottage, perhaps popping over to the historic Crumplehorn Inn for a sneaky aperitif or a glass of traditional ale. As it's only the shortest of walks away, it would be a shame not to enjoy their hospitality.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;On the first floor you'll find the first of the three beautiful bedrooms, with its own en suite shower-room, along with the family bathroom. A wonderful room with a separate shower for a morning 'rise and shine' rinse and a glorious free-standing bath for a lazy holiday soak.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Heading up to the second floor you'll find the pretty double bedroom and twin room. Set under the eaves, with exposed beams and deep window seats, they are full of charm and everything you would expect from a cottage bedroom."/>
    </cottages>
    <complexCottages/>
    <regions west="581" co="380" cofw="60" cosw="57" conc="98" cobm="0" cosc="165" de="161" deno="79" deda="12" deso="70" so="14" do="26"/>
    <total total="381"/>
    <geography wkt="POLYGON ((-5.71769 50.06727, -5.67993 50.032, -5.55702 50.04699, -5.53092 50.0871, -5.47073 50.12318, -5.46913 50.12244, -5.42861 50.09635, -5.27 49.99935, -5.24803 49.97418, -5.21438 49.95342, -5.1828 49.96005, -5.16494 49.98875, -5.09696 50.00067, -5.06469 50.03156, -5.05096 50.05052, -5.07745 50.12626, -5.00564 50.13554, -4.77836 50.21997, -4.64996 50.30162, -4.216 50.30732, -4.1724 50.31324, -4.14115 50.33757, -4.17583 50.36298, -4.18836 50.36348, -4.18716 50.37306, -4.20845 50.39713, -4.20231 50.40972, -4.20416 50.41431, -4.20244 50.42032, -4.1954 50.4317, -4.20355 50.45094, -4.21737 50.46624, -4.22381 50.46368, -4.22642 50.4583, -4.23093 50.45674, -4.23849 50.4646, -4.22381 50.47264, -4.21853 50.4749, -4.21737 50.47772, -4.21788 50.48274, -4.22286 50.48984, -4.21926 50.49317, -4.22063 50.49729, -4.21806 50.49803, -4.21033 50.4962, -4.20312 50.49164, -4.19342 50.49328, -4.19368 50.49814, -4.18476 50.49825, -4.17892 50.50163, -4.18253 50.506, -4.18399 50.50878, -4.18716 50.50818, -4.19154 50.50709, -4.1942 50.50338, -4.19995 50.50305, -4.20295 50.50425, -4.2008 50.51397, -4.2093 50.51397, -4.20544 50.52003, -4.21205 50.52892, -4.20742 50.53165, -4.20613 50.53339, -4.21463 50.53547, -4.22458 50.52969, -4.23385 50.53176, -4.24089 50.54311, -4.24737 50.5445, -4.2535 50.54447, -4.26818 50.53568, -4.2717 50.5371, -4.27042 50.53918, -4.26578 50.54261, -4.26046 50.54362, -4.25908 50.54518, -4.25861 50.55153, -4.2626 50.5569, -4.2778 50.56971, -4.27762 50.57473, -4.27307 50.5768, -4.26968 50.57909, -4.27136 50.58258, -4.27874 50.58462, -4.28681 50.58481, -4.28582 50.58206, -4.28224 50.57916, -4.28217 50.5765, -4.28424 50.57565, -4.28672 50.57544, -4.28887 50.57697, -4.28938 50.5816, -4.29088 50.58432, -4.29565 50.58454, -4.29986 50.58375, -4.30647 50.5791, -4.30808 50.58262, -4.31123 50.58544, -4.3117 50.59141, -4.30591 50.59399, -4.30537 50.59844, -4.30775 50.60252, -4.30501 50.60701, -4.30346 50.61156, -4.30578 50.61469, -4.30488 50.61686, -4.30706 50.6187, -4.30222 50.62531, -4.29977 50.63378, -4.31166 50.63844, -4.32171 50.63636, -4.32192 50.63641, -4.3222 50.63666, -4.32242 50.63698, -4.32272 50.63703, -4.32308 50.63722, -4.32461 50.64095, -4.33129 50.64239, -4.33474 50.65612, -4.33837 50.66144, -4.34397 50.67002, -4.34339 50.67792, -4.34796 50.68479, -4.34741 50.68934, -4.3515 50.69378, -4.36466 50.69847, -4.36671 50.70847, -4.36362 50.71298, -4.36071 50.71879, -4.37049 50.72618, -4.36963 50.73267, -4.37392 50.73721, -4.37847 50.74552, -4.38377 50.76331, -4.38976 50.77014, -4.4086 50.77033, -4.41512 50.76534, -4.42954 50.7775, -4.44945 50.78532, -4.47074 50.794, -4.44448 50.80897, -4.44096 50.86686, -4.42439 50.87097, -4.44568 50.89025, -4.45632 50.92976, -4.55692 50.92771, -4.93286 50.59718, -5.05096 50.55532, -5.29976 50.26435, -5.30502 50.26476, -5.39566 50.24237, -5.43804 50.19557, -5.47599 50.21821, -5.49728 50.21909, -5.54054 50.21557, -5.67581 50.16766, -5.71563 50.12762, -5.71769 50.06727, -5.71769 50.06727, -5.71769 50.06727, -5.71769 50.06727, -5.71769 50.06727, -5.71769 50.06727, -5.71769 50.06727, -5.71769 50.06727, -5.71769 50.06727))"/>
    <regionTotals uk="0" sw="0" co="0" cofw="0" cosw="0" conc="0" cosc="0" de="0" deno="0" deda="0" deso="0" deea="0" so="0" do="0" cw="0" wi="0" gl="0" se="0" io="0" sx="0" ke="0" ha="0" nf="0" cy="0" pb="0" p="0" ca="0" gw="0" con="0" ang="0" ce="0" sn="0" mo="0" cd="0" st="0" wa="0" db="0" he="0" li="0" pd="0" ne="0" yo="0" ny="0" yoe="0" yd="0" yow="0" cu="0" nu="0" la="0" ee="0" nor="0" su="0" sc="0" sch="0" agb="0" oh="0" ih="0" iom="0" ioms="0" iomw="0" iomn="0" iome="0"/>
    <description criteriaDescription="For a 1 week holiday between 03 Nov 25 and 10 Nov 25."/>
    <sorting defaultSort="sleeps-ascending" currentSort="sleeps-ascending"/>
    <metrics elapsed="0.594988"/>
</results>